got my hands on an LG g5 let's jump in
and assess the build quality through a
series of relatively logical durability
tests this one is definitely unique the
battery has a little button near the
bottom that ejects the cartridge out of
the phone you can also detach the
battery from the base of the cartridge
just by pulling on it apparently you can
also add other toys to the end of the
phone as well like a camera module kind
of reminds me of those old-school
gameboy accessories the LG g5 has a
screen protector pre-installed so I'll
pull that off before we jump into the
good stuff I have a series of pics with
different tips on them and they allow me
to see where the hardness of the screen
falls on Mohs scale of hardness notice
how thin the glasses though you can see
the pressure of my pic against the LCD
it's probably good for the cellphone
weight and cost management but it does
not have a very quality feel to it nor
will it protect the LCD very well if
it's dropped the LG g5 has Gorilla Glass
4 so it doesn't scratch until level 6
and then a deeper scratch with the
seventh pick which is on par with other
smart phones these days the camera lens
is made of glass which is fantastic
considering they have more than the
usual amount of cameras back here one is
a normal camera and the other is a super
wide angle lens not as wide as a GoPro
but still wider than any other cell
phone either way it's protected with
glass and not plastic which is a good
thing the fingerprint scanner and power
buttons are made of plastic as well as
the back housing this is not a premium
filling phone by any means I tried
scratching up the fingerprint scanner to
see if it would still work after heavy
abuse and surprisingly it worked just
fine recognized my finger and would
unlock the phone I'd give that a thumbs
up for sure here's the burn test this is
another phone with an IPS LCD display
very similar to the iphone SE that i
tested earlier today the iphones pixels
turned off after about 16 seconds of
flame the LG g5 pixels turned off after
only three seconds then burned
permanently and left a white mark having
a thicker glass like the iphone and
samsung's would protect the LCD better
and give it a more premium feel you can
even see the pressure of my finger
against the LCD during normal use now
when I first got this phone I
for sure that the end cartridge would
snap off like a piece of chocolate
during the bin test you can see how
Wiggly it is with just my fingertips
with a full-on bend in progress the end
piece will flex in both directions like
a 680 dollar pez dispenser but amazingly
it does not snap off I don't know what
kind of black magic they used to secure
it in place but the phone still
functions one hundred percent and passes
the bin test this is my 19th smartphone
durability test hit that subscribe
button so you never miss any of my
future videos it's totally free and
thanks for watching hope to see you
around