our lonely patch of the sky just got a
little less lonely with the
identification of a rocky earth-sized
planet neighboring the star closest to
our own Sun on August twenty-fourth 2016
researchers announced the exciting news
that they had positively identified a
planet about 1.3 times the size of Earth
orbiting the red dwarf star Proxima
Centauri 4.2 light-years away the
researchers made the discovery by
observing the star carefully over long
periods of time they found that once
every 11.2 days the light from the star
shifted ever so slightly a variation
called a Doppler shift during which the
star appeared to be moving toward Earth
slightly and then away from Earth
slightly that wobble indicated the
presence of a planet but it's closest to
us in distance and size isn't the only
thrilling thing about the discovery the
researchers also pointed out that the
planet orbits the star in an area that
might be considered habitable if Proxima
be has managed to hang on to an
atmosphere and liquid water it might be
hospitable to life there is no guarantee
that the planet has either an atmosphere
or water Proxima be orbits Proxima
Centauri every 11.2 days at a distance
of 7.5 million kilometers or about 5% of
the distance between the Earth and the
Sun for comparison mercury orbits the
Sun at an average of fifty seven point
nine million kilometers if Proxima
Centauri were like the Sun the short
distance between the two would be enough
to at least fry the planet's surface but
Proxima Centauri is a much dimmer
smaller star and at that distance of
less than eight million kilometers the
researchers estimate that the planet
would get about sixty-five percent of
the radiation that the earth proceeds
without an atmosphere the temperature
and Proxima B would be about negative 40
degrees Celsius that's really cold but
if earth didn't have an atmosphere our
planet would be a chill negative 20
degrees Celsius so we can't really talk
the distance is close enough that if the
planet managed to hang on to an
atmosphere it could potentially support
water in a liquid state that's if the
planet formed in such a way that water
in the protoplanet didn't just vaporize
in the early solar system or if it had
water delivered to it by comments later
in its life if you're noticing a lot of
ifs that's because a lot is still
unknown about our new neighbor while
computer models suggest that the planet
could hold water or an atmosphere or
even a magnetic field which would help
deflect deadly radiation from the
planet's surface there is no evidence
yet of any of those things unfortunately
heading out to Proxima Centauri for a
visit might take some time well it is
the closest star 4.24 layers is still a
very long way and getting there would
take thousands of years with our current
technology check out our episode on
light speed travel which details the
trip to Alpha Centauri and the
difficulty human space and getting there
until we can develop warp drive or some
other awesome tech that would allow us
to launch a robotic or manned mission to
Proxima be we will have to content
ourselves with telescope based
observations of the planet and rely on
those observations and models to tell us
more about what our closest neighbor
really looks like in the meantime our
generation will be defined by the
continued discoveries of other
potentially habitable worlds and our
continued quest to prove that there is
other life in our universe as Carl Sagan
once said somewhere something incredible
is waiting to be known
want more click here and watch our video
about the possibility of traveling to
Alpha Centauri and don't forget to
subscribe thanks for watching