this is Eugenia Cooney's face from 2012
she has a decently healthy-looking face
and since then as you can see things
have changed quite a bit since I started
making videos addressing Eugenia
Cooney's obvious eating disorder you
guys have posted quite a bit about her
to an EC on XYZ most messages people
post both productive for myself and for
Eugenia there are negative messages that
people post as well people say things
like it's horrible your video so you
insult a girl with an illness but it's
fairly clear they're ignoring the key
points one clearly at least 9 out of 10
people understand that Eugenia Cooney
actually has an eating disorder and is
lying when she says she doesn't have an
eating disorder - he's been repeatedly
proven that Eugenia Cooney making her
outfit videos and numerous other videos
showing off her on healthily skinny body
is triggering numerous young girls who
starve themselves as well so he has
someone who's lying to us and someone
who is irrefutably hurting others due to
the clear evidence against her that she
is in fact hurting others but 3
something you should understand is that
the point of me making these videos is
not to hurt Eugenia Cooney but I want
this to be my final video on Eugenia
Cooney despite the fact that a huge
amount of you have shown significant
interest in the last two videos I made
about her mostly because of the
following you guys remember me talking
about this screenshot were actually
looked up the texting question to find
out if it was legitimately from her
tumblr and then I realized it was in
fact from her tumblr I also noted that
she had thousands of other posts on that
tumblr dating all the way back to 2010
what seems like there's a 99% chance
that Eugenia found out about her tumblr
being the Achilles heel to her story
that she's not anorexic as someone on
the forums brought to my attention it
seems that Eugenia has deleted her
tumblr and I ask you does that seem like
the behavior of someone who has nothing
to hide or the behavior of someone who's
running from the truth you go to the
tumblr that was linked directly from her
own youtube channel at tumblr she's been
working on since 2010 and it is now
completely wiped out no links no
pictures especially no posts of her
talking about her disorder as someone
responded with wayback machine saved it
if you do in fact go to that URL you'll
find lo and behold there's her tumblr
significantly as it was before I made a
video addressing the fact that she was
lying to you guys and I say fact with
little doubt at this point because an
honest person doesn't delete their
tumblr that's of course is something
significantly shady going on again if
you click on archive at that URL a small
percentage of the post that she
previously had still show up
fortunately before Eugenia wiped out a
lot of her posts forever this user
already proven to post accurate screen
caps in the past also more recently
posted the following someone says so
happy to see that you're putting on
weight you look healthier she says um
I'm not putting on weight someone says
you're getting fat please stop eating
she says I can't tell if you're being
serious I haven't gained weight though
so I don't know how I could be getting
fat and sitting on the same as I was
before the person says you're so pretty
you really need to gain some weight your
arms and legs look really strange she
says haha ok well thanks for saying I'm
pretty but saying my arms and legs look
kind of strange is kind of rude whether
one's a gain weight or not as my
decision stop so here she is again
admitting she doesn't have a medical
condition is a clear contradiction to
anyone saying that she's naturally
skinny garlis within this message she
admits that it's her choice as the one
that she gains weight and she clearly
states that she does not want to gain
weight meaning she is clearly actively
doing what's necessary to maintain the
weight she admitted that she was around
which is 84 pounds while also being what
she admitted she is 5 foot 9 according
to banner health calm the height you're
supposed to be if you're that lights is
4 foot 9 or 4 foot 10 meanwhile you Gina
Cooney is supposed to be 131 to 160
pounds so that means she's about half
the way she's supposed to be I believe
it's fair to call that certified dying
here's a decently old photograph of
Eugenia do you see how our legs are
those legs almost look like they belong
to a healthy human being let's see how
our legs are doing more recently there
yeah this is a picture from weeks ago
and here's a side-by-side comparison and
a lot of people feel like it's a
solution to ignore her issues as if
that'll somehow make her get better
I assure you pretending like everything
is okay to a person who's clearly
suffering an eating disorder that will
only aid in a bed their crimes against
themselves there's another picture of
how Eugenie used to look in this
perspective she looks like a normal
human being they're numerous videos on
YouTube now that are even from friends
of you genius who know her personally
expressing concern for her well-being
more people than I can recall who were
formerly anorexic have come to me
sharing their story and also their
disappointment with Eugenia Cooney she's
not listening to the tens if not
hundreds of thousands of people telling
her she has a problem and telling her
that she is triggering others creating a
potential lethal problem for them as
well it's important to note that Eugenia
Cooney's condition is so severe that a
lot of the people who were formerly
anorexic I've expressed sincere
frustration as to how she at this point
cannot admit the truth she's shown how
dishonest she is by deleting her tumblr
and doing other things that I pointed
out in previous videos it's evidence in
the mass majority that she is purely
wrong it has been made clear to her
without any doubt that what she's doing
is hurting people this has even gotten
so serious that news articles have been
written petitions have been started and
yes even the producers of dr. Phil tried
to reach out to this girl who one
exploit her for their own profit just
like many people including myself have
gained attention by talking about her
and to as dr. Phil often does sit her
down and tell her like it is he actually
did
reach out to me because producers or
whatever but I don't really want to go
in his show honestly cuz the reason I
think he like wants me to go on is cuz
of like all the crazy videos being made
about me don't want dr. Phil I'm not
going inductors hello guys if you just
want to go on and be like friends or
whatever like hey what's up dr. Phil
that would be cool classic Eugenia
running from the truth now if dr. Phil
asked me to go on a show because he
thought that I had a problem I would
love to see what he had to say and you
know what I would probably agree with
half the stuff he said because I'm sure
I'm not perfect and I'm sure there are
things about me that could improve but
Eugenia Cooney is terrified of admitting
that she's anorexic thanks to her trying
to cover up her Tumblr posts and it's
more evident now than ever that you
cannot trust her because people who are
friends of the truth do not try to
remove the truth from the internet again
the examples go on and on but here's
someone who posted I've lost 12 pounds
and eat what I want as long as I have
one meal a day I plan on trying to get
as skinny as Eugenia Cooney she's so
effing perv and they're asking other
people how they lose weight there's a
site called body visualizer calm here we
have a pretty recent picture of Eugenia
Cooney side by side this woman there's
obviously a very significant difference
let's go and modify things till they
match up so a 5 foot tall person is 60
inches
Gina Cooney is 5 foot 9 though she's 69
inches he is how we're definitely not
154 pounds let's go and bring this down
so it looks similar to her alright so
the lowest let me drop her 259 pounds
let's see what that looks like all right
so that's what 5 9 and 59 pounds looks
like let's compare the two you know what
it might just be my opinion but Eugenia
Cooney actually looks slightly skinnier
eugenie on you now said that she was
about 84 pounds according to body
visualizer this is actually what five
nine and 84 pounds looks like do another
side-by-side ya know appears that among
the many things Eugenia Cooney seems to
be dishonest about her approximate
weight could be added to the list
unless of course by about she means
within 25 pounds so that's not logical I
weigh about 175 pounds and I'm not going
to tell someone that I'm about 150
pounds that would be a blatant lie
regardless I know I can make plenty of
more Eugenia videos to get millions upon
millions of collective views from them
but I am officially resigning from the
topic anyone can help Eugenie at this
point it's probably her mom and I'm
simply not willing to reach out to her
mom and contact her because to me that
doesn't feel appropriate I also don't
feel like it's appropriate to call the
cops on her spite the fact that if
someone did call the cops on her they
would no doubt take her into custody as
her behavior is obviously suicidal
considering anorexia can take 25 years
off your life and I personally seen
police haul away people because their
danger themselves before only to not let
them
until they felt like that person was no
longer at a risk to themselves I could
definitely do either of those things
which would probably help her but I am
NOT Eugenius personal friend so I will
not personally contact people in her
personal life I have done as much as I
think is appropriate as someone who was
her former online acquaintance by
addressing this issue online exclusively
we now know that Eugenia Cooney is in
fact a danger to herself we also know
that her condition is only getting worse
so for the sake of her life and the
lives of the countless young girls who
are actively emulating her behavior
truly do hope things work out for the
best