hey guys it's Eugenia since today is
need to be using a makeup tutorial kind
of video with a brand new palette that I
got I recently did another cat funny
video on this palette which was the
alchemist holographic palette I really
like to tell it up and I just actually
got another cat fun v palette this one
is brand new I'm pretty sure to Brandi
pot and it's called but the pastel goth
palace I was super excited to get this
because I really liked the pastel goth
style I was like wow that's a cool name
and then I saw that it was like a palace
of really nice colorful I Titus and I
always will love colorful eyeshadow I
think it's really really cool I usually
excited to get so yeah super excited
that I just got this palette and I was
playing with some of the colors of my
eye and pretty much i got my eyes to
look like that this is like with a
couple of the colors it's kind of like
trying them out so i have to date i
would show you guys how I did this
makeup off with this palette and also
show you guys all the colors in here and
yeah it's a really cool product so i'm
going to show you guys now so this is
new how it that I just got it's super
cool I actually am just opening it right
now it's called the pastel goth palette
I'm so sir the Chinese because I love
Kat Von D products so I'm so excited
chance out and the trial of colors I
thought the package is so cool to this
and the way that the letters walk on
here are so cool like I really like to
design a nice I thought it was super
often and this is the power it comes
with eight colors and a mirror digitally
cool so it has yellow I'm so excited to
China because i always like to have a
really nice vibrant yellow because when
I'm wearing like yellow and I want to
have yellow eyeshadow to notch it then I
would love to have a yellow eyeshadow
and it always reminds me of pd to you
just like speak to it's the best credit
has this really cool shade called
clementine and it's kind of a foreign g
kind of pinkish data so it looks like
then there is too kind of like purple
issues yeah and dope just like really
cute cat kind of shade I don't know and
dope because it's just stupid joke color
so
getting the news do it sounds really
cool gloom gloomy and there's dagger
which is like a grayish finish shade and
yeah well go nevermind skull huh and go
with the white shade so so I'm just
going to like try some of those am I I
student I'm not even exactly sure like
what I'm doing with my makeups so I'm
kind of just doing this as I go along
after them also see you guys in my skin
so you can kind of see how all the
colors look it might not show up as good
as in my eyes because oh my eyes I'm
gonna use primer and all that but that
way you guys can still kind of see how
it looks and yes okay i'm going to try
some of the colors now so the greatest
thing that i'm going to do before i
actually even put any of these
eyeshadows on i'm going to use my Urban
Decay primer potion so that way the
colors should appear a lot better
exactly sure what colors I was going to
use like I said I think that first I'm
going to take this shade Clementine
which is kind of like this for appt
shape and i'm going to try putting that
kind of like just in the inner corner of
my eye and just like putting that kind
of like a little bit throughout their
ok so that's that I just put that on a
little bit and I really really like this
color I feel like it's really pretty
it's a really nice kind of like peachy
shade so I think it's really cool then
kind of like on the Rex would i think
i'm going to try meow which is a
personal change think that name is so to
you because it's like a cat and cast
your office like what I hear me out it
just makes me want to like put on my cat
headphones and I'm going to put that on
my I now ok so that is that shade right
there on my iPad so I really like this
shade I think it's really nice really
kind of like my last shade of purple and
I feel like it goes really good with
like the teachers gate I feel like they
blended well like really well together
so I really like how they blend you in
easley so I think now unlike the crease
kind of part of my eye I'm going to use
the darker purple which is called soup
and see how that works so that's the
darker purple also like blended into my
eyes I feel like it's super super nice
it blends really really well at the
other colors I just realized that you're
probably doing the other I at the same
time so ok I'm going to like to but I
already did to the side to the other I
really quick
you
[Music]
alright so now both I feel like in the
same place i also just took a blending
brush to blend the colors together a
little bit more and the next thing i'm
going to do is how did you like the
highlights above my eye and I'm going to
try the white shade which is coughs all
like what I need up ok so that's the way
to eat I feel like it's a really really
nice white face would be like a white
eyeshadow I feel like it works really
good now I'm going to go under my eyes
and not sure exactly what I want to do
is like I said I'm kind of just like
doing this as I go along I really want
to try to blue shade though which is
zoom right there so i think i'm going to
try that underneath my eyes she's like a
little brush to do not alright so now i
have two blue underneath my eyes I deal
with the blue works really really good
it's a really really nice really bright
kind of blue I really like blue eye
shadow so definitely one of my favorite
colors that I've tried but now this is a
really like part of the palace but I
hope they're just going to do eyeliner
and mascara real quick because I always
like to have that with my eye makeup and
i'll show you guys how needs actually
look in my skin so you can see all the
colors
[Music]
I thought well those are my eyes
finished so this is how they came out
found them done so i really really love
the colors in this palette and I feel
like super awesome palette and also i'm
going to show you guys just kind of had
a look on my skin so that way you can
see all the colors and also the colors
that i didn't use today cuz there's a
couple that i didn't use because i think
it would be kind of hard foods like
eight colors of my eyes like in one go
but yeah i'm going to try to fit if you
guys just like on my skin a little bit
so the internet colors I actually think
they showed us really really well on my
arm which is cool so that's them all
actually in order well backwards order
huh and yeah they super nice and I
really like how all the colors are like
a very nice and pastel looking but they
also a really bright and really show up
and see really pretty so I like them a
lot they're really cool here show you
closer up to 15 your arm is actually
really hard to get all the colors to
show but hopefully you guys can see them
okay like I think you can actually see
them pretty good which is good so yeah
hey colors huh so I just say that I
really love this palette I really feel
like all the colors are super pretty and
they're really cool because they're run
really nice kind of like pastel kind of
shapes but they're also pretty bright
and I really always love like colorful
bright eyeshadow I feel like it's so
nice to be pretty and I know
like the Great and white shade too I
think they're really good and just like
at a sell golf palette like really good
style and it's really cool so you guys
enjoyed this video and you like seeing
the sneakiest tutorial and me showing
you these colors make sure you give this
video a like also guys reminder if you
didn't already notice that if you give
this video a thumbs up you will be an
official member of my official calls I'm
actually the cult leader somebody made a
comment once this being like me saying
like the video if you like it is
obviously me being a cult leader so yes
I can totally confirm that that I am
later of my home so if you like to join
the costs and all you go to do is give
this video a thumbs up also subscribe to
my youtube channel if you want to be
like a VIP cult members yeah I post
videos of here a lot and you can also
click on the bell icon if you want
because that way you'll be notified
whenever I post new videos I love you
guys so much a cop you guys in my next
video all right hi
[Music]