hey guys it's achieving yet but not too
long ago I did one of those videos it's
like a boyfriend does my voice over
video I don't actually have a boyfriend
so I just did with my friend here Jordan
it seems like a lot of you guys really
liked that video so today I thought I
would make another one of those videos
only today I'm going to be doing it a
little bit differently hi I'm Eugenia's
grandmother I'm gonna do the makeover
you're gonna do the voiceover right
grandma do the voiceover you're gonna do
a great job oh thank you it's a little
note to me but it's very easy when you
get to it step by step it just Falls
right into place and I'm very happy to
do it as far as we saw this I learned it
it's a little difficult than anybody
that wants to take that job step by step
it's well worth your time and your looks
if you're interested in your looks
believe me try it step by step so i'm
going to show you guys how I did my
makeup today I just finished doing it
not too long ago and then she's gonna
like voice over it and tell you what I'm
doing so I'm going to start the video
now and if you guys like it hi I'm
Eugenia and what I'm doing is my makeup
first of all you don't sell soup here
Europe for my errors I did that first so
after my here I did my eyes and a little
bit of makeup first here and there color
is perfect um and I make sure it's right
on one eye and then when I that's
perfect i will go to the other ride um
if you look carefully you'll see how
beautiful is coming I have a lot of
assistance though from Virginia who is
really the professional person that
helped me out my first place and so if
there's anything you want to know you
can ask me
I'll go to the authority um ok now I see
him doing really well that I just come
yells good and if you notice how
carefully I do it oh yeah it is coming
out really well and then we'll go to the
next and um I will go from step to step
yeah I did it very very very good um see
you can see she can do a little time to
look at it while she puts it on and
you'll notice the color the shade
everything is perfect so if you want
grid eyes she's close up and you will
see what she's doing and you can just
copy it which will be exciting easy for
you to
I want to put it away carefully and I do
want to get it on my eyes yeah so a
little bit i will talk a little bit you
don't have to just kind of you know look
and see for yourself which is wonderful
because seeing is believing okay now I
noticed um I think we're doing we're
almost done we did as much as we could
on one eye we're on the other ride and
the makeup is going on nicely there we
go if you look you'll see how perfect
it's being done you're so easy when you
see if I just tell you my product but
you see exactly what you did or did you
can coffee and come out just here we go
[Music]
can't resist the one eye to the other
eye everything has been pretty much
caught up and can build in there
[Music]
okay now um the year is done and see how
beautiful and silky it's done it's just
gorgeous the face is done we do it in
steps if you say cheese
[Music]
okay um I'm doing it as best I can do it
if you'll notice it's a lot than done I
when I started out there was no makeup
now I'm almost done completely the eyes
the makeup the hair and it will be a
beautiful result and you can see how
easy it is when you see a person do and
that rather than not seeing it right now
and putting my makeup on and i'm putting
a little bit of Rouge in and then you
have to worry about the cheekbones they
have to get yours you have to make them
look just beautiful and then come when
that is done you go to the other side
the other cheek bone make them perfect
both to match and I see you're doing all
that and then as you were doing with the
bottom of the cheekbones it's just
coming out perfect but you have to do it
step by step and you can hear is a step
and then now she's doing um to still in
the temple the temples belong to you
tell me about you can't just do the same
you've gotta treat those temples like
this and now I see whenever you get to
you know you're gonna do your cheekbones
and they are coming up ahead and tell
not only the cheekbones you've got to
get your
pianos has to keep out perfect okay I'm
done why kill subscribe very good
[Music]
you