sorry conga Masuka car gel seen in play
house gets painfully real for fans the
past six months have been a roller
coaster of emotions for a long time fans
of car gel whose on-screen reunions
burned hopes of a real-life
reconciliation until their friendship
was supposedly ruined by negativity and
unmet expectations on Monday former
sweethearts Angelica Panganiban and
Carlo Aquino parted ways all over again
at least on screen with their respective
characters in the daytime series
Playhouse saying goodbye to each other
and exchanging apologies after a failed
romance in the February 25th episode
Harold Aquino said sorry to Patty
Panganiban for only belatedly informing
her of a fellowship he is taking up in
Singapore for three years prompting the
latter to ask whether the decision was
the result of their falling-out Gus took
on malam and mon august unga's took oh
not IM young tail patty told Harold /
August hooker real cos I'm aging fair
CEO
hindi naman pew Eden sapling young Pegg
mama hana i the big a co co CAHSEE
minson young support cooling sorry
company Geetha
sorry column Asuka she went on a Corinne
nent a Corinne Amasa
a masa akan magma bago young/nasa Paso
Co Peru Hindi PHA a baka Hanina although
visibly hurt
Harold conceded he said he has long
known he could not possibly replace
Marlon sanyo mundo in Patty's heart I
know you tried Farouk ahead and in God
mo oka had a nun Phillip Corinne we both
know that I cannot be that guy
it will always be him
he said the on screen parting at least
to some car gel fans who shared online
their reactions felt painfully familiar
following the recent developments in the
personal lives of their idols in early
January Pangani been courted headlines
when she declared her intention to
distance herself from aquino saying
negativity from fans affected their
relationship the rent appeared to have
been triggered by one follower who
censured Pangani been over her cryptic
posts about love that supposedly made
Aquino vulnerable to judgment
a week later the actress spoke of being
hurt after having loved again she went
on to ask followers on Twitter to help
her move on from the past boyfriend who
also happens to be a play house co-star
both descriptions that fit Akeno at the
time
rumors of Akeno dating another woman had
just surfaced following viral photos of
him apparently on vacation with the
model
[Music]