hey thank you yes cited a video is
actually going to be sponsored by a
really really great company called
inspiring and inspiring actually sends
me the shirt says I speak fluent sarcasm
because both houses just agreeing with
speak up and this is actually a c-54
great france because this bridge is a
lot of great things this brand is
actually about helping people who go
through things like anxiety and
discussion and mental illnesses and i
think that's a super great pub because i
know that life can be really hard and
that sometimes you know a lot of people
go through really hard things that it
definitely do a risk and really hard so
i think it is really really great with
this brand does with helping people
willing to tough times yes i definitely
recommend that you guys checked out to
clothing too often clothing lines and
actually with all of us as they sell a
portion of all the money that is Lena
neutrik actually gives you helping
people with things like anxiety
depression and mental illnesses so it's
really just lost so i'm going to put the
lace cute inspiring break down there and
description so if you guys want to go
and check them out that i would
definitely recommend that and okay i'm
going to sting you guys soon as I
favorite with your outfits now I
actually just where to start I love you
both and I kind of wanted to meet me
with your out this video in anyways okay
I'm going to show you guys I off its
mouth so hope you guys liked them and
actually this is what is the new items
that i actually just lost from co-op
outlet and i love this up in so much
this might look like a sister shirt I
was like I was
distant you know and amongst people
thought this is anish ears but secret
sexually not is the shirt so this is the
shirt it's like sweat it earlier but
it's kind of just like a cool where I
think also he probably school Pettis on
the shoulder thing that I thought that
was feeling folded edges and also i have
on its roster and you didn't notice
about me i have like into rebasing for
five shirts fear Allah last really
remind me of like anime girl because i'm
using those really to animate growth and
they always have easily cool my sponsors
and this is a red and black one and in
this is kind of like a jacket that i
think so good with this and really like
worst of all things and put it on
backwards oops okay please do it right
how do you get to mom oh yes okay
backwards is so this is how flips off
it's not real fur throws it seems i know
i know we're milford it's totally fake
for so he's not real so guys but it's so
cool really nice important task to do
sushi bar codes off of me he's like one
of my viewers in you know and we service
if you miss me if you need finish their
hands so yes you want you to do is good
with spicy shoes would like I don't know
so here's another specimen from our soup
so yeah actually I think narcissism
please watch my uncle in these videos so
sorry work but if you thought that was
good for you natta no need to watch all
the videos they know if I ever seen
anything special like that that's not
very slick that nothing we've got like
good subtle things like being sitting
Zoe's of fun cool things to do you know
this is the next posture by gosh I feel
like this one actually goes Super Girl
and everything I need some pretty much
because it really does like color
schemes like a 16 hour and this is
another Oscar is like a great and flat
posture so that's it and this is like
the same thing we're just me feel like
things like animating will profit and
women pretty much my favorite kind of at
yourself yeah that's distributor also
got it I just need your poisonous up in
the first year so I am where this
message it just in case you didn't know
I love this cat and go like in Texas
meet all of this to wait for and also I
do this picture respond to just like
whatever I really just think we're
especially in the winter because it's
really cold out they make your legs
feels like a little bit warmer and just
being completely related except this is
the next year that I thought and I
thought it was a treo is beautiful at
shirt as beautiful and just kind of the
shirt with some straps and it's kind of
like triangular depends like change your
design and sabbatic so Jana up it and
honestly this appalling 8030 fold out so
we're in the winters but I feel like you
can still make it work on you don't
worry jacket or you could just like be
really cold or you know this week so
yeah I don't know I realized to shoot
that sell its neck shirt and also I feel
like to share the molecular this church
it was kind of like a high-waisted skirt
so which way you can kind of like
and then shit works and cat silly silly
fool I just totally sick for like every
ailment know what the people do that
once bidding was a suit like me video
games I hope we actually won't do that
but yes let's keep in this video like
Bing video a look I don't know why
before so that's gonna get to know
whether we're does so such as I think of
this but I hope people my life sitting
room is like super like yay sitting
right out specially marked cuz I know
Mark like really really likes today mr.
move it the market often love you mark
oh and by the way I want to see in the
research my tears just looking like
Julie Julie bass throughout this video a
lot of time like what I started out to
be I'll be like oh my hands of games the
Bettles I can't keep doing it and
executing someone totally getting super
messed up so Emily's argue with that but
anyways so this is a flutter kind of
thing so I successful because on the top
it just kind of happy place headaches
there and it has it on both sides that
they will both are cut out and then also
the back of this fired it's like so cool
despite all the pattern ok alright so my
hair is additionally kind of falling
apart you think like pretend I'm we're
going to land in my car through so much
would split up thanks but please like
what you're not looking like that so
again I just wanted to everyone car
through my hair's getting really messed
up throughout this video but both you
guys and let's not keep you for that I
don't know anyways next outfit so this
next year is next to sell em too much
and it's just kind of like a black as
like cool please look just like a photo
manager so you were just football
spotting them and yes that is assured so
this is the next year this year actually
has obviously cool products on it this
year is just like totally set out and
and also on your neck it just kind of
have like this cool thing where you just
kind of like high it against bullying
darling time actually it's kind of like
a buckle thing and just kind of like put
a few days and then you go to school
like things around your neck I don't
actually know exactly what you call
these histories but that's the kind of
shirt surfaces and um thanks it is a
nice shirt that I want to show you guys
this one is a white shirt like wow the
colors known so she's going to be right
there I have always liked still kind of
fear which I thought was awesome by the
way good I want to speak up I know that
like a melon suppose I don't look you
guys to do it but I noticed no price
tags on me just be advised no I did not
feel any of these clothes why not steal
things their clothes or anything like
that so you know these are all this new
and I haven't obviously mortensen yet
for the most part of an unlucky one
because it's bit like brand new so I
haven't touched on surprise myself yet
still feel it inside past the hats why
so steel feeling son and this letter is
actually the last letter that I wasn't a
few guys and I got excited look so cool
because this one is just like super cut
out like everywhere on it so like yeah
all over it it's just like all these
cutouts like throw on all the pleas of
butter who's even cut up there and I
think on that side to stay fed up yes
there is and then also like all down
there through there and they kind of
just like keep continuing on down it
everywhere and it's good because it like
it's like you're warm but it's also like
style of cut-ups everywhere which is
often so you got this letter is actually
very last thing that I can usually fool
and we do outfit or usability weird
ideas like whatever you guys follow me
around I don't know I don't really at
least like just refuses I just kind of
like weird but I feel like where you can
really Ruby's like from ever you wanna
wear them you've already knows notice
right now but I have anything different
on but see you may actually not do exist
that you've actually had all a space net
and soft a different style but I
actually soft and i got these are simple
and they're really good because they
just kind of like cling to your leg and
they feel exactly like how fishnet feels
like they feel the same way very much
and as we can see sexy what you regard
with great and I was diuretic do so hope
I don't centrally corner somewhere those
Asian sites I think it wouldn't think it
was um Sandra and Susan and say or
however you say that so I feel like I
truly do that with this and it look like
works really good well thank you guys so
much for watching this video and if you
enjoyed watching this video or even you
like anything that I showed you or if
you like to my kind of dependence
because beating is just like the coolest
thing in the world to do like last year
everyone goes into like stabbing and all
that I definitely think this here
spinning this is going to take over the
make sure you did this video like I'll
give the video a like of course if you
want to do Michael so that obviously how
you join it you just give bailey and you
join my magical often cult and subscribe
if you want to be a VIP members occult
person you want to be often we know what
I post these videos and also you click
on the bell icon you should actually be
doing fide ever if this new video on
here hope you guys liked the video and
thank you guys so much for watching I
love you guys bye
you