hey guys it's Eugenia so today I'm going
to be doing an outfit Hall of a really
really cool site that i recently found
online I really love like why fashion
and quality kind of stuff a lot of
things from Japan so I really like that
kind of style searching for Kawhi sites
online I found this really really cool
site called Sun wednesday i'm actually
not entirely sure if i am saying their
name right i'm not sure if it's like
solid rents or San runs for San ren say
but they're really really cool site and
they saw some really cool clothes so
when I found them there is so much that
I wanted on your site so i just ordered
a bunch of stuff i took a while to get
here because it does all come from Asia
so I didn't think it would actually come
even it's like soon as it did though
like I found that the other day it
actually got here like the day before
Christmas and I was just like yay this
is so exciting I have my clothes so I
wanted to make like a hall kind of video
and show you guys what I got and just
try to one for you guys and if any of
you guys are interested in buying any of
the items that I show you in this video
then down there below I'm gonna link to
sound run say your son right sorry I'm
saying is like you're on I don't know
but yeah like them down there below and
they still a lot of other cool stuff on
their site tooth so yeah so the first
thing that I wanted to show you guys is
actually the outfit that I have on right
now they listed as a buzz online but
it's kind of like a sweater whilst kind
of thing I guess I don't know and these
Kevin a lot of different colors I got it
in this really pretty pink shade I
thought it was a really cute color are
pretty very material they're actually
super super soft they're pretty warm too
which i like about that since I get
cooled a lot I'm also wearing a skirt
that is actually also from this site I
thought this was a very very cute skirt
so the boat was actually a pin on Bo so
you can really put it wherever you want
you could put them in the back if you
prefer to have it and back of the skirt
because yeah it has this design on it
throughout it or if you want to you can
do it i did and just kind of put it on
the front because i thought it looks
good
so that's where I put it so the next
skirt is a blue skirt it's just kind of
like a pleated skirt and then yeah I
just I'm just super cute let's get this
little button right here so yeah and
there's a zipper on the side basically
everything on this site is mostly like
side zippers at least like from what I
ordered I think so this is another one
that I got thought it was really cute
it's just a black skirt and then it's
kind of like a layer kind of skirt I
guess you could say because that over it
has this kind of like additional player
that's black and it's just kind of like
a clear kind of like sheer black and
yeah so that's the skirt I actually post
a picture on Twitter of his yesterday
committing it's super super cute so this
is basically a jacket like the reason
that I love this so much is that it had
these adorable bunny ears huh yeah I
thought that was so cute like I
especially like lots of the funny years
so yeah thought they was super super
adorable these are little like paw
prints gloves all fingerless which is
perfect is that way when I'm using my
phone I still can use it because my
gloves are fingerless the red jacket
it's really good for like in the Windsor
when you're cold or things like that so
yes so that's that's this jacket and yet
as you can see it's just kind of like a
foyer to kind of jacket so just kind of
like pops out there and yeah this is
this they are like a white nice talk
with these little like black stripes
going on the top throughout them so yeah
I got these for an awesome pair of socks
I put this skirt back on because I
realized i forgot to show you guys the
actual top that goes with it because it
goes to the top that is also really
really
similar to the anime school drop it so I
have the only thing that's like
different with it is it's like a bit of
a longer top right there so yeah also on
the top it has this little like fabric
piece instead of just kind of like a
solid color it has this really cute like
pattern it's like flowers on it and all
of that so I got another pair of
over-the-knee socks and this is another
pair of over knee socks that are in pink
these are super cute because they also
have these little bows on them so you
can just kind of tie I'm not sure if I
tied it in the right place like on this
one I was kind of having some trouble
like figuring out we are the little
string thing goes into I feel like I can
never have too many pairs of these
software like you so much this pair i
know that i do have some tied right I
think when the other ones i may have
like tie the bow on the wrong side cuz
oh yeah on these bows you kind of like
strengthen through these little holes
you kind of need to go like in and out
of bowls up but yeah I think they were
so cute with the ribbon and I really
liked this power it's just kind of like
a red head of maroon kind of color
though the next shirt is this super
super cute capture I got this is really
awesome and super adorable just a really
cute shirt on it with this cat right
here I said he was really cool wookie
that it was a really cute shirt so yeah
that is my cat shirt and then i'll stay
i got these which these actually look
like a pair of knee socks or overturning
socks but these are actually not so
these are actually appeared
sighs and I thought these are so cute
and I just like I gotta get these
because if you did already notice about
me which you probably do because got
like a good amount of him around yep but
I love Pikachu so much I know he's like
the most common no pokemon but he's my
favorite because he's just so adorable
and I can't help it and I don't do so
much in the past I've had a long days
that were like cat penna tights with a
little cat features and these heads are
actually Pikachu has that they were so
cute and they went like fall out with
these like in the back it's actually
Pikachu tales do so yeah in the back
efficient lighting Dale is this just
kind of a black shirt it's long sleeves
and if it is really cool but in the back
it's actually like open credit cut
really cool this is another skirt that i
got from there I thought this was such a
cute skirt it goes pretty go with this
year actually because I don't know
they're both black that's kind of on the
bottom it's kind of more of like this
grayish color and I was really really
cool because it's kind of like a layered
type of skirt and it was super cute
because it's good the boo right there on
the side so um yeah this is another
sweater that i got from this site it's a
really cute spotted just like a short
its water it kind of has this cool like
clearing style so I likes thought about
it it just kind of has it like that
throughout the sweater yes
the next bag is this pink dress I hope
this pink dress is really really cute
it's just kind of like this cool kind of
like sheer material throughout it then
they said I let you do with it is on the
side it just kind of came with this
little tie I don't know if I really did
like the best job tying it right now so
it looks kind of weird in some sections
and that's probably why so sorry about
that we gotta use kind of tired and then
makes it fit really good and yeah that's
this dress this is a white shirt that I
got from this site I just really like
specified sure a lot I thought it was a
really really cool shirt so this shirt
has a collar on the top as you can see I
kind of threw here it just kind of has
all these lines and then yeah so that's
the shirt it also came with this black
little ribbon thing but I'm honestly not
sure exactly it's just how it's supposed
to be worn I'm probably actually going
to check the vector in the website from
when I ordered it and see if I am
wearing your right cuz I'm not really
sure if you are so as to where it like
the way I have on right now I'd remember
so tie it in a bow or just kind of like
tie it like that kinda or just us to
where it is like around your waist high
early don't know but yeah I really like
this shirts a lot but it was a really
cool white shirt so yeah next item I
thought was really really adorable it's
super super soft like the material is
really really nice very warm which is
awesome could these cute little balls on
it right here and in something
I thought was so so with warm with this
right here let's get this Kitty thought
that was really really cute oh this big
also has a hood kind of like had a buddy
one has a head like this one I think it
supposed to be some kind of like
dinosaur monster kind of creature and on
the back to it doesn't just have these
ears it also has a tail in the back and
I love that about this I think it's so
cute so the next thing that I want to
show you guys is this light dress I
thought this is a really really pretty
white dress it's kind of like a dress
that you button up right here then on
the collar it has all these pretty
jewels so that's there I'll so this bow
that actually is on the dress actually
comes separately I think it came with
the dress but actually is kind of like
put that on with it and then it makes it
look a lot better because it definitely
makes it like it better and all of that
so yes just like a white dress with a
black bow the next thing is this kind of
bluish green little shirt kind of thing
and yeah I said this was super super
cute pretty loose and but it's kind of
meant to be like that and it's really
really soft like that's something that I
really like about this website is
everything was just super soft and cute
it has all these little flowers on it
throughout it so yeah that's the shirt
also i have another pink jacket to show
you guys it is like super super soft
it's like this nice free super super
soft material coolest thing about this
it has ears up so yay these are sea
very cute I'm not sure this supposed to
be like cat ears or wolf ears or what
exactly but basically anything with
animal ears I almost always loved it so
yeah I looked at about this that it had
these years and it also just has these
little pig strings here I'm guessing
these are two just kind of to tie it or
something I mean it has the buttons to
you but I guess if he will still want to
tie it then I don't know but yeah these
are here this is another way dress that
I got from this site I just thought this
was a really cute white dress it's just
kind of a white dress with some layers I
guess if you want to call it that I
don't really know exactly what you call
it when there's like a layer of a dress
but that's just what I'm going to call
it back think it lowers a little bit and
then yeah this is just a white dress
that I thought was really cute when I
saw this pink skirt on the site I
thought it was super super cute I really
wanted to get it I really like these
kind of skirts and dresses and things
like that really kind of just like filed
a little bit so then right there there's
a bow and I'm not really sure honestly
if this bow is supposed to go in the
front or the back um it doesn't really
have like a tag on it like how a lot of
clothes have so you kind of know what
site it goes on I really think it really
can go on wherever you want it to go I
just kind of liked it with the bow in
the front so that's why I'm
to go in the front right now this is
another pair of tights I got this is
just basically a black pair of tights
but they're super super cute because
they have these little fuzz on them with
a little jewel all right there and then
on the top they kind of turned a bit
more sheer this is another pair of socks
that I thought and these are black and
pink striped socks I think that these
goes super super well with this skirt or
probably look a lot of stuff that I
ordered I just really like the
combination of black and pink I feel
like those two colors look really good
together so yeah I really like these
socks lot so I really like garters even
though I don't have too many I've always
thought they were really cool so when I
saw this when I was like ah this is the
coolest that I've ever seen past this
hurts here which I thought was super
cute and then all throughout it it is
super super studded I love studs I think
studs are awesome so yeah that's my
girder
[Music]
this one might be kind of a weird thing
to stubbing you guys but for some reason
for a really really long time I've
wanted an umbrella not really for
probably the reason that most people
want an umbrella to like you know stay
dry in the rain but more like a fashion
kind of umbrella just because for the
sake of the looking cool pretty much so
yeah I ordered an umbrella it actually
even came with a little umbrella case
it's really pretty even if it wasn't
raining I think I think it's kind of
just like a cool fashion kind of
umbrella the purple umbrella and then
the inside is really really awesome it's
actually kind of like a galaxy umbrella
not really like the galaxy that everyone
is obsessed with I like that galaxy two
that I do it I like like a lot of
galaxies stuff is cool but um it's kind
of like a bunch of stars and it's like a
nice guy there's a moon there's just a
bunch of stars throughout the inside so
yeah I thought it was a really really
cool umbrella next thing is this black
skirt here this is actually technically
escorts because it has shorts well this
but yeah this is just a cute black skirt
[Music]
the next thing is really really cute you
probably can't tell what it is yet but
it is a yellow hoodie but it's not just
a yellow hoodie yeah so it's Pikachu yay
the hood has Pikachu it's got the
Pikachu years and all of that but on the
sides here it actually has two what I
think our paws I know that Pikachu it
doesn't have paws I think it's just kind
of supposed to make the jacket look even
cuter than it already is so yeah those
are the paws on it and this is my pic
you honey go by the way guys this is
really random but I realized that also
in this package I just I just kind of
realize this I can't discuss with the
umbrella because it was in with this and
the umbrella and there's an app package
don't really know exactly and you get it
on or what it even really goes to but it
is this little cute fair right there
this bear with like these beads and
bleep so yeah cap just cute to not show
you guys besides clothes from this side
I saw a lot of stuff on this is there
not to appears choose from this site and
this is the first pair that I got it's a
black pair of heels they're basically
just a black heels and then they have a
bow right there and I like those a lot
so you're really pretty and then this
was the second pair of shoes that I got
to use are a purple kind of lavender
kind of color they're kind of similar to
the other ones to have a bit of a
thicker heel and then also these also
the bows on them so those are all the
items that I wanted to show you guys
today if you guys liked anything that I
showed you or if you enjoyed this video
at all make sure you give this video a
thumbs up so I know that you liked it
also subscribe to my youtube channel if
you want
no when I post new videos because i post
new videos a lot you want to click on
the Val icon and you'll actually be
notified whenever I post new videos so
you can watch my videos whenever I post
new ones thank you guys for watching and
I love you guys so much I'll see you
guys in my next video all right bye guys
[Music]