hi I'm doing a cooking show but first
I'm gonna do something I care about to
prove to you guys that I do eat some
cucumbers are you ready for me to prove
you guys wrong freelee the banana girl
in their knees now oh I love cumbers o
CI love food oh so good for my tummy six
today I'm gonna cook some stir-fry by
the way check out my outfit of the day
[Music]
it's okay a little bit and succeed it
down here ok so I just add the name food
here yeah ok so now we need to add
flavor me a salt and pepper and onion
stuff I know I'll just sprinkle water on
my fingers Oh favor gotta wipe off my
hand now wouldn't want to absorb the
water calories hey there just gonna turn
the burner so while it cooks let's go
ahead and read tweets from other
youtubers this tweet you stupid and read
bitch eat some food that's what we're
doing on this here I know the one thing
I suck on her act in life is penis that
doesn't have anything to do with me but
thanks for the confession seriously get
some help you Gina call one eight
hundred nine 312 237 know how many
cucumbers do I have to eat to prove to
you that I don't need hat yummy just go
scrape it onto the plate there there we
go everything a day comes the moment of
truth water favorite rice is my favorite
oh gotta go to the bathroom you
shouldn't be concerned I go to the
bathroom through my mouth so it's okay
[Music]
now before we get to dessert let's read
some more tweets I'm taking bets on when
that part of the bones you call a body
is going to fall apart I have a hundred
dollars on you being dead within a week
I don't know how to respond to that so
I'm just going to be fake polite haha
thank you if I sneezed on you and your
weak little body exploded from the wind
pack alone does that count as murder
barrels I don't know science too well so
I can't answer me sane and naturally
skinny so why is your mom so fat i got
like that question you go girl you don't
need a man to feed you or anyone for
that matter because you don't eat
lolololol even Tom there's no how to
feed themselves idiot I thought jenna
Marbles was faced with in that oh my god
Bernie Sanders tweeted me Eugenia has
repeatedly been proving the trigger
young girls to starving themselves her
existence on YouTube is cancerous and if
she
had any respect for audience she would
either start didn't care of herself her
stop making her triggering outfit video
showing off her shriveled dying body
today desirable wait findings on this
part of me okay so what I do to eat
dessert is this stop going to take a
ziplock baggie and when you're done with
the surgery just throw away trash so all
the lovely insects can eat it right in a
mine gene can we stay
[Music]