oh dude what the hell what so hard you
blocked it oh yeah Oh
nips McGee
Oh
all right Sean your first painting as
far as you can
great give him a karate chop Randy's
neck all right you kick a - groin you're
gonna squeeze its hardest no no you know
what that I did hey guys why don't we
just all attack him at the same time
Ryan not gonna make You Gino you talk
like that I never told you anything I
love you had to tell you before right
no Ryan not gonna make it gene you talk
like that I never told you even left the
soda can in the freezer ray left a can
of soda in the freezer you don't take it
out it's gonna explode what who cares
about that you've just been shot don't
understand if you don't take it out it's
gonna go everything I don't care about
the freezer I don't care about a stupid
can of coke I care about you coke from
him because I love you what what are you
doing Ryan this isn't funny I know
you're still alive I can feel your pulse
you know what even if you do live
through this don't expect me to be
around anymore and I hope that stupid
coke does explode in your freezer you
jerk g2 sprite damn it Charlie is the
blue one or the red one just caught red
blue white black which one anyone cut
the way no again it can't be the white
one Charlie cook then cut the blue one
it's not the blue one either red Telling
You Charlie it's not the red and it has
to be the black one whoa what the hell
man what that is racist what I think
just because it's the black one that's
the one that needs to be cut what are
you talking about that was the last one
I told you to cut you should hear
yourself right now you sound like a
racist basketball coach listen we are
running out of time just cut a quiet
line this was your choice not mine
you did it I did it you did it
damn it Charlie is the blue one of the
red don't cut any of them just flip it
over flip it over okay take out the
batteries
all right the batteries out still climb
down - all right well look for an outlet
around got it plugged in yes okay so
unplug it still counting down Charlie
humming all right listen okay I want you
to just cut all the wires at once what
wires or what makes it work if you cut
them all at once it'll probably mess
something up are you crazy I'm not gonna
do that
I'm just Yolo okay kid you did it okay
so now the alarm clock is off what what
do you want me to do with the bomb
get up against the wall turn around
yeah hold on you know I expected a long
one it was too easy so easy that I can
pour myself a cup of delicious tea I can
enjoy this cup of tea carefree without
even being worried about being
interrupted mid sense it was too easy so
easy that I can pour myself a cup of
delicious tea I can enjoy this cup of
tea carefree without even being
interrupted mid-set wipe yourself off
man
you did without even being interrupted
mid-sentence wipe yourself off man
you did are you supposed to say that
after issue is Justin riffle again I get
to lethal weapon to reference but that's
supposed to happen long live the king
okay well that would actually did happen
before the kill but my king doesn't
really have nothing to do ah tea huh
we're like teehee okay so now the alarm
clock is off what what do you want me to
do with the bomb too easy
tea huh
more like tea so thank you guys again so
much for watching if you want to see the
behind the scenes in bloopers click the
one on the left if you want to see the
last expectations vs. reality I think it
was like relationships or something like
the one on the right and that's all
there is to clicked today so yeah