hey there I haven't made a video on
eugenia cooney's weight in months my
videos on Eugenia Cooney always do very
well so as a person who's concerned
about Eugenie's health and a person who
wants to make successful videos I'd like
to take the opportunity to publicly
check up on her now type in Eugenia
Cooney there she is over a million
subscribers partially no doubt thanks to
me I mean one of my videos on her got
over three million views some of those
viewers had to translate to subscribers
to her Channel so again Eugene yet
you're welcome and thank you so you gina
has ignored basically all of my videos
despite the popular response they got
this video about Eugenia's actual
weights which I hope was an eye-opening
video 59,000 likes 4,000 dislikes or
Eugenia Cooney final video 75,000 like
6,000 dislikes most all of us want
Eugenie hakuna to get help but she
doesn't want to get herself held and her
mom was in one of her videos three weeks
ago so clearly her mom is well aware of
Eugenia's condition but as for some
reason decided not to do enough as you
genius still suffering so this is
Eugenia on the twelfth of februari sorry
I'm struggling here I'm kind of at a
loss for words just looking at her legs
she obviously hasn't paid attention to a
single goddamn thing I've said she's
obviously still starving herself and
she's probably like what 68 pounds she's
5 foot 9 and weighs less than one-third
of me probably she's still gladly
triggering anorexic girls around the
world I've gotten tons of tweets tons of
people messaging me about how her videos
are triggering and she does not give a
shit could not be more obvious she
continues the worst skimpy outfits in
her videos showing off her starve body
and nobody's doing anything about it
that's awesome just want to stop real
quick if you are triggered by this video
and now you want to starve yourself just
want to emphasize that you are insanely
fucking stupid and if you don't want to
be insanely fucking stupid and please go
feed yourself being stupid means you
lack intelligence or common sense and
starving yourself is not common sense
that's the opposite of common sense even
the dumbest dogs know to feed themselves
so understand what you have is a
dysfunction to dysfunction and your
brain and also understand that skinny
people starving themselves will not make
them more beautiful it will just make
them ugly will reveal how ugly your
brain is as it is clearly defective and
will make your body look unappealing and
defective as well when you hear oh my
gosh you're so skinny it's not a
compliment it's a recognition of your
clear ab normality and many but not all
cases an indication that you might have
an eating disorder so hopefully I
figured you and we can continue to
observe footage here Eugenia did a
makeup tutorial thank goodness at least
in that video she's not triggering
people with her body and oh my gosh can
i just say how beautiful Eugenia Cooney
would be if she was twice as heavy
that's right twice as heavy as she's 70
pounds right now he should be about 140
considering she's 59 I was once with
someone who was 57 in 135 pounds and she
had a great body so you think I would
know considering I had sex with that
person Eugenia has a video called how to
get a guy to fall in love with you say
so yeah that's what this video is gonna
be about I know I haven't really been in
too many relationships other than was
like Jack Skellington but the fact that
the first person who came to her mind
when she talked about relationship she's
been in is a fictional character from a
Tim Burton film know a guy who literally
is dead because he has no meat on his
bones eugenia take a hint you know that
just seems a little bit odd to me
doesn't it seem odd to you the first
thing that comes to remind regarding a
relationship and emotional connection
with someone is a creature beyond
anorexia and has another big f you to
the world Gina made a winter outfits
video only two weeks ago and it got
mainly dislikes because a lot of other
people are as pissed off as I am as she
keeps triggering people knowing she's
hurting people with her clearly anorexic
bodies yes video the King I thought we
actually won't do that but yeah but
t-spin to this video like spitting video
almost I don't know why he foresaw says
it's gonna gonna be down by the way guys
so so I could think of weird but I hope
people that like spitting
like super like yay spit it out so a lot
of people think that I called for
Eugenio cooney to be banned from YouTube
in the past I actually never did I
specifically address people wanting to
get her band and I said that she
shouldn't be bad as I'm not confident
that that would cause her to feed
herself especially if that's her primary
source of income you know how are you
supposed to buy food if you don't have
money but if you are a friend of Eugenia
cooney's or if you are a family member
please contact other friends or family
members so you can form an intervention
and confront Eugenia directly there's a
phone number that can be called to help
Eugene young with her eating disorder
the girl clearly needs to go to rehab
please remember that this is no joke
anorexia actually has the highest
fatality rate of any psychological
disorder it is highly likely that
Eugenia Cooney is killing herself and
statistically around one out of every
five people she inspires to starve
themselves is going to wind up killing
themselves meanwhile while some
countries are thinking about banning
anorexic websites I don't see anything
showing up about how anorexia itself is
illegal while suicide is illegal in many
states this is unfortunately a gray case
so we have Eugenia cooney's family and
friends not caring about her enough to
force her to get help because if I were
her family member that's exactly what I
would do with the consent of local law
enforcement our drive her to a rehab
center myself ginia Cooney herself isn't
listening obviously despite how many
videos people have made on her despite
how much support those videos have
gotten she's not listening to you guys
who have probably by now made millions
of comments regarding how insane her
treatment of herself is of course
YouTube themselves haven't banned
Eugenia no dad because the potential
drama that would cause now generally
risky that might be Eugene yet so many
people have proven it you are risk to
yourself at your current state is
unhealthy if you ate a normal healthy
diet weight would no doubt go up and you
with a normal healthy body at the age
you are people would be much more likely
to click on your videos and want to
watch you for an extended period of time
considering you're already a likable
person your problem is that you're
killing yourself in most everyone's
season but I realized why I haven't made
videos on this for a couple months why I
showed a disinterest never making videos
about Eugenia ever again before because
no one can really fix Eugenia but
Eugenia and she's clearly unwilling to
help anyone help her sell and by the way
Eugenia your videos have actually hurt
people that I've cared about if
indicated to me in private conversations
that's significantly in part because of
you and your videos they have also
starved themselves but I understand that
you are also a victim a victim of
yourself