thank you Jeannie ask for today I'm
going to be viewing a smash or pass
video I can see a lot of people doing
these kind of videos on YouTube and I
thought it would be cool she's also
doing these videos I thought I could
actually do this so with a little twist
so instead of disputing in normal
masterpass video I'm actually going to
be doing this is Disney characters so I
wanted to Twitter and I like you guys
asked me a bunch of like Disney
character Mattrick passes not your past
by the Vegas I feel like that sounds
like so sexual and I am not feeling a
very super sexual person so this is
thought super sexual videos don't worry
guys this is totally not like a porn
vide or anything like that so like don't
worry you know I feel like the napping
could you see something super cool if
you guys remember like a while so our
various like Nigel you would always just
feel like wow that fit washing there's a
game super smash bros if you're going to
like smash with someone could go and
play mass whole day we're gonna do like
hey like let's not play this hangout you
know so it's like it's totally friendly
turn or we're just going to pass and be
like no we're not hanging out with that
person thats also means but we're we're
passing for whatever reason i'm going to
like read what you guys sent me now and
tell you guys if I would smash or pass
to disney cars if you guys sent me your
I was totally smashed with your here is
great i am sitting here so cute and I
feel really bad for York because usually
lonely a lot and I don't want him to do
a late I spend a lot of time alone too
so your looks like what smash hang out
with the best friends hola hmm but I
want to face than that just because he's
in a snowman and so many cute I think
did it really like frozen too much even
have everyone like love prison but I
don't got passing oo oo could easily
friendly at night and you snowman so I'm
like a mixed but I guess we'll smash
most place natural haha oh my gosh whoa
I think of some type of Alliance I don't
know i'm not actually maybe not a lot
and I can actually no I don't think it's
a lot of never mind but I no idea with
this guy's scary though it a little bit
evil so I'm sorry this guy if I'm wrong
if you meeting is nice and easy not evil
sometimes looks can be deceiving you
know I'm going tuesday passed by the way
how does this crusty old bitch get your
necklace oh my gosh this guy doesn't
wear a necklace woke up for democracy
old men but I'm good because if you look
like you might possess my soul bleeding
out if you feel like he's white eyes was
like no pupils or anything I just feel
like he wants to do this me so I'm going
to see half what are you from choice or
what kind of pictures is this so oh my
gosh okay well normally I'm a face mask
I love woody woody is my favorite toy
story character but this picture for the
safe house is then scary where you going
to find stuff area area is gonna be
smashed she's totally cool year by the
way with always attached using the
piercing and I would actually love to
hang out with Ariel Ariel has always
been like my favorite Disney Princess
though yes and turn me into a mermaid
going to be so fun because my trading
places like should give me a human on
albion mermaid gonna be great and then
like jacob visit me in to defeat we'll
hang out we super gone through wish from
Snow White I'm going to pastors and few
seems really evil he tries to make the
white eat like an evil apple or
something I really prefer if it happens
to me and that I don't like how that
happens it doesn't seem fun while
they're all definitely smash responders
vomit you so much fun foods or ammonia
six is around whoa this is like Elsa and
frozen is pictured and a few with like
like like like like slick support richer
fremont so is this kind of crazy
pictures I'll smash else's not like that
so light
I know that would be cool if I had to
pick a favorite frozen princess I depict
also that cuz I look like the coolest us
and sprinkles so she's cool even if
she's an ice princess to like she is
cool so she can teach me enough be cold
then cold all the time Cinderella not
Cinderella this is such an offer
something video me and Israel are gonna
hang out we can go like finally shoes
together so yeah Matt beast from beauty
in the beast mass because he was
actually really nice I think that beyond
like a really beautiful soul and that's
like Bella and started falling in love
is when she found out the kind of person
anyone even if you looked scary she fell
in love with who he was just a beautiful
thing which he fell in love him for who
he truly it I think that he seems like a
beautiful creatures so yeah not so we
need a few match we need to do is so
cute Hercules I've actually seen
Hercules but i'm going to thank much her
Joey seems like a cool very heroic
person Mickey Mouse not obviously used
to King he's like the king of Disney
like everyone busy he's the king so get
a smash me he's the best submitting is
coming I'll at something McGee like but
I think you are like so much for this
like more spaced out kinda me mouth I
think max is he's bitchy mission awesome
Aladdin hmm not a lot of exterior might
be kind of astro doughnuts and I used to
be assessment so yes alice from alice in
wonderland i would love to hang out with
Allison Allison was there is to have
face to not because to be cool to see
creditors he seems like a cool person
like that tool like magical Wonderland
and I certainly don't be so cool to do
that Peter Pan max Peter Pan is awesome
he has like a young soul forever scar
from the lion king oh my gosh pass some
scar from the lion king stars terrible
he nixed easily statuses like that bad
things dozen white pink so I definitely
do not want to hang out with him meebo
is dick oh my god i enjoyed you smashed
both at us there was so often into you
at such a good movie yesterday it does
count okay guys if you don't cut their
Wars characters then you should because
Disney technically on Star Wars out and
I love story so as the servers in here
and I think not the devastated because
even though i'd normally I want to pop
the nose and not like be playing smash
events for like hanging out for whatever
her theater is a great villain he is
often so mass Prince Eric Massey is such
a cool print he's probably my favorite
Prince I think on Disney princes cross
why do not know what croc is from if you
found my efforts me groove or something
I've seen this show like the efforts me
schoolgirl whatever but I actually
haven't seen the aspiration you provide
update but hey you look like a nice
friendly guys so yeah looks like smashed
hang out no way despicable like take
your hair like those punk at it Alice
max you're not going to hang out with
the evil witch so next hero oh my gosh
mass Europe and a max Q I love big hero
6 so much joy I haven't seen emotions
but do I looks like she's just oh joy so
oh my god thank you guys for sending me
your smash or pass it I really hope that
you guys like this video give it a like
if you liked it beautiful on you guys
liked it I don't know
Beyonce another why maybe I'll be like a
Pokemon one or something and subscribe
to my youtube channel if you want to see
more videos for me also you'll be a VIP
member of the calls all you're going to
do to doing the call to give the video a
like subscribe for like a VIP members
cult it's super easy also be sure to
click the bell icon you want to be
notified ever I post a new video because
once you press that it should tell you
like I cook and I was videos a lot I
ready Joe so much i'll see you in my
next video okay bye
[Music]