hello I made you my big cock may come
over look can't we are we ready I'm
gonna be beautiful haha hey guys today
I'm here with my mom hell of a night so
excited so excited again and I'm going
to do something really cool tonight like
she actually came on today he's like you
know me cause we're able dutiful you are
known you longer to count is 2 so this
is like you know a anime habano I'm
actually believe you can make it for her
and if you do I'm gonna need her lip
service I mean you already look
beautiful but i'm going to make fun okay
all right i excised using my makeup so
she did that normally use my makeup like
normally so just use internal makeup who
use an ominous you know that yeah these
lines this is open tomato but not like
you now make me email making some sue a
little i do good okay it should be very
beneficial of it and a foul I mean it's
going to be a good experience okay but
was giving me a look like oh oh here she
goes yeah you know first time we didn't
know you had such following some places
I go people actually recognize me which
is really scary you're a come on this is
your cup of tea maybe I sequester my own
sake I didn't want to measure only if
you can also make your own YouTube chill
I would subscribe we on alright so we're
going to do your own bacon so this is my
foundation ok I think me mum when you're
in different colors ex-wife okay look
I'm gonna like kale person but ok
inside you don't put anything under all
people do like I don't feel but I put
like the green address block south as
red as I have but that's okay a
beautiful are you ready oh you're in
Italy is all I combinations oh ok you
don't put my job I'm here labreche I
don't feel any fun day sorry Jeff sorry
oh yeah wonderful thank your makeup
she's like a soap yeah really feels only
joking so exactly I make up feeling mom
como a spa through this trophy right ok
ok so i can you type ok so you like
using a brush I always did the brush I
like you is fun it's like spongebob yes
good I can't there bouvet I wanna see
some za swimmy aye captain here the
tricks i respond to go home the best
time to enjoy sweater oh my god when you
wear this dress sweater with one with
the color run with the car Carol nah you
don't know i don't like spongebob
whether you want once the haunt andy is
an advocate to know when an interesting
i like them we have the jingles like
this isn't like you know so is turn on
bedrock Jeremiah
a benefit is really quick I think it
looks really good so far right okay like
I said no gelatin hi all open suppose
this little bit oh wow she's with get
makeup little it not blended foot please
closing rate it feels good he'll
remember I'm going out now get some like
Tyler y-you don't know where I later no
what's your phone well that's a big
reason if you look so shiny I will wash
or grandma's rooms really happy yes okay
all right thank you weapons at this spot
a little the fuel to my errands come on
what try my vinyl turn off is today but
it looks really what it's like
highlighter you don't like it highly to
be good foster 8300 have a sauna on top
what are you doing I'm doing away from
facebook be finalized the finale every
rock but yeah okay but now we're gonna
do your eyes yes good one okay so let's
look Holly love you something very
neutral purple I really like a music
purple will be purple yeah like a muted
her braces we got this ahead I'm mission
unify man painted all timing this is
really John now it doesn't like me so
like you think you know we could just
the prior a toast it is it hi so sure
the community is good for men
by the end of the day but surely the
ticket okay I get there soon mr.
Napthine importance of the white color
color is going to you are a natural oh
this is natural rate which ok just jokin
I are gonna do this by opposition yes I
feel like it applies better to use me
and great idea before of torque toys
down I am getting excited yeah it's a
little bit darker when it goes on so I
thought I'm gonna look for the light and
dark alone with you Oh with you oh he's
not chancing it to feel a little bit
done do you have any sisters you don't
worry all new power oh yeah this dream
or not there's like that ladies like
this green a lazy people would go this
way let's remember we go back that's you
love me now the right margin great lunch
this is squid over love it sorry I
realized it now I want to go ahead and
put its lending in the comments but like
I all I think I think I know Sarah I
don't want you thank you all right rear
this one the ball enough to put your
ugliness
I'm all such great thank you put the
oddball doing I mean so fearful oh yeah
but with you out of all handsome or one
more run of all I have to play the other
way so it's where the eyeliner okay
ready alright nobody knows yeah yeah I
like yeah Michael oh yeah I can sense a
feeling like oh yeah aye captain come
again what was that any other patterns
your fav Sandy Cheeks and love her oh
she's got a cheap stuff yeah csb and we
go underneath oh I was looking at
Waterloo Oh like look boy sleep it's
done oh you're gonna put even while I
know you want I could you like the Eagle
spongebob you would hide on Eva homicide
oh my name is in the law oh honey i have
nokia c6 receive us but I stop pull it
off are the email all your bad for a lot
of a multi-city my under cyclic send it
oh don't give you look kind of point
work than i doing Oh door
open it to China just a little already
to do on a second person i feel like i
do I like Lucy take over the line
darling you are doing what kind of like
ego but thanks to my daughter walk ah
that are individually that's over you so
it's going to finish the way too much
drama I'm going to fight all you want to
be a hairy I know you're going way over
was a good a doubling today ok I get
this words like oh I love it and it's
supposed to be a way ok look at me here
only be two ee do you want to double
within the other line well I'm good so
I'm just going your license and no no
you know what's right doll thanks
natural titties don't you remember I'm
drunk if you want like holographic lips
from the club cuz i wanna make a nigga
pull it looks really good not actually
works LOL seriously it worse I'm really
good like you looking to do you know if
you like sushi
you were talking about happenings are
Hollow nothing like sorry now also you
want fair nice it was really cool see
like 10 to be very cultured this
actually thinks is this the life you
bang it somehow because the color keeps
like not being very tolerant words wow
you look so good you think I haven't
really used to it all right good why
should I slide it off I think I did oh
god I look like a freak against
eyeglasses all they go how do you hate
my hair up give a lot of life give a lot
to life so I might make it up I think I
used to my channel ok gives me an idea
to fuck whoo scary because the eyebrows
did he really won with you ok I'm going
to do a colorful like a giant I've
actually never done that for services I
know Tetris I used to talk to fuck
impart my upper back when I has to like
Jenna Lyons and I guess what one day my
eyebrows ever really grew back I want me
like somebody get more people just like
my videos and like sums up this really
the thing that is cool all because of
the dungeon I think I'm it's like I
honestly afraid I am I've experimental
guinea pig in from working what are we
trying to pull that with you I want to
make your eyebrows look purple and I've
never done this before we're going right
back to email you your second was in
your brows yalda okay I mean age or over
that purple so let me try some ahead of
highlighters that we're fighting about
both work with more love for people who
are reminded working I don't think it's
like
second so girly but it kind do you don't
keep that is my long beautiful makeover
that I've tried to do a good job and
hopefully I am here color now what are
you going to be like it and i want to
express the world with my dues makeover
please like the video like the video
look and if you do we don't take another
one and you keep us some ideas what to
do we get 25,000 life I'll do your
makeup is all made very beautiful and
then she can go out and maybe just do
well his loss right so ready come to
make over here we go baby all right and
I did I'll do it to Bill your life I'll
do it like oh maybe YouTube here oh yeah
five like it up wake it up yeah I coming
down here okay right now I can't go no
idiot like the day outcomes and using
see it off I was doing very well that
was a shocker oh my god alright it's
beautiful Bible really do look like I
don't know how to do my makeup I did you
can kind of need yeah oh my god yeah
she's been ok hey so makeup artist 25
ah
[Music]