hey there Jackie strobe amateur units
here and this is the start to the London
vlogs I kid out the wait to show you got
ya coming I'm just filming stop for the
video hey can you help me with this
stuff let me take this up yeah oh are
you ready for your trip across the pond
yeah you're not going thankfully oh
that's okay but I hope you carry your
bags oh I got my camera bag in my
luggage he needs all this things you
know getting that camera on the way
there yeah you're gonna get it on
[Music]
playing this Widow
I have a hard 14 actually just playing D
s yeah it's Luana planned yeah it's just
sense yeah just a das not a 30s you're
just bored say you got dust on your
hands from that dinosaur you're playing
well Yoshi Yoshi
Oh Jesse don't you want to put it down
Singham oh my god he is furious right
now does this ring figure you're gonna
get married when you're over there on
the British Isles you know nobody can
even hear you because there's too many
cars coming I'm glad oh but seriously
you're gonna gonna do something he's
like wait could I still play my games
and I still play I love my mom what the
freaking do the part guys I control the
camera now me my dad guy like maybe
wonders - ever since when do you care
how I dress oh my TV show yeah yeah I
could dress up maybe I want to support
Master Chief who's on my shirt you don't
even know
that's art this better man Yello
now we're into take turns holding the
camera so we in document trip but I want
to be in front of the camera you're
gonna be in front
that's my youtube channel
you can't go seven hours without playin
because this drill is I can't even
charge my D s with these plugs they have
these like washing machine plugs it's
not even normal
[Music]
please
hey guys it's the end of the first night
pretty exhausted and just to make
matters worse share bed with my dad spec
enough room to be a bit like what I have
boxer briefs on like 90 percent of males
wear this shit I don't care I don't want
you to put some clothes on this bed god
forbid I'm comfortable at bedtime at
night seriously look at how you doing
I'm playing D s I do this every night
it's therapeutic that's a break you just
go to sleep
geez you come on this trip baby I played
a frickin game at night yeah we're not
doing anything we're in the freakin
hotel room
thank you
everyone came for one of these it was
kind of not I'll spread my butt cheeks
for Shrek strike his love let's check
his life
foolish Englishmen leaving their lights
which was on the outside of the bathroom
my dad's me shower I'm I shut the light
off on
[Music]
is this all you've been doing all day
yeah
can't you go outside I've been
videotaping all day yeah big deal I've
been out all day videotape no it's
London Bridge Buckingham Palace is cold
and raining why would I go outside and
expose myself to that shit but who cares
about the weather you got your in in
London just come on seriously I'm
storing things in here what does it
matter if I go see some buildings it
matters a lot Leisha could been out with
me with you that game does nothing for
you give me people a lot and I met
people in game don't you so now there's
other people in here I don't care I know
you don't care cuz I only involved in a
stupid game it's not soup dish yeah that
really hemorrhoid cross you're gonna
fucking destroy hey hey here's your ten
what you're lucky you are lucky this
isn't broken
[Applause]
[Music]
sometimes that's what she didn't exist
is that that bad I was having a good
time till that happen