hey guys it's Eugenia today I'm going to
be doing a morning routine video I've
seen a lot of a type of videos on
YouTube and I've also had a lot of
people ask me to make one of these
videos but for some reason I've never
made one I've made a lot of like makeup
tutorial videos and hair videos and
things like that but I've never made a
morning routine video so yeah today I'm
going to be doing that and um yeah I
guess I'll just show you guys like what
I do when I wake up and how I get ready
this isn't really too much of a morning
routine kind of video because a lot of
the time i actually will have a very
very weird sleep schedule and i will
wake up at like 12 or later sometimes it
just kind of depends this and that's my
sleep schedule will get like really
crazy anyways okay I'm going to show you
guys my morning routine now hi guys so
of course the first thing that I need to
do is wake up though when I wake up I'm
usually wearing this it's like a hello
kitty robe so this is usually when I
sleep in and then when i wake up i'm
usually this cuz that's kind of how that
works I guess huh so yeah I've awake now
my bed is not really made that great
right now but I've been in California
the last few months and now i'm back
here in connecticut for a while so um
when I came up here from there I
couldn't bring on my bedding so right
now I have a different bedding so I have
Pikachu this is pretty new ish oh my
Pikachu comforter I bad just not made
that well right now so sorry about that
I yay for Pikachu I wish I had Pikachu
pillows deal I feel like that would look
so much better with this also just
remembered that I spend a ton of time in
the morning doing this I spend a ton of
time on my phone here a lot at a time
when I wake up one of the first things
that I'll do before I even get out of
bed is just going my phone and be
checking Twitter Instagram and all of
that and my emails and youtube comments
and just a bunch of stuff that can be
pretty addicting being in your phone so
sometimes I feel like I will just be in
there for like a couple of hours even
sometimes just like checking stuff next
thing that I do when I wake up this is
one of the first very important things
that I do is I brush
my teeth everyday hugely I'll come in
here and get a toothbrush my real
toothbrush is actually charging right
now because it's like an electric one
but this is one of my travel
toothbrushes it's not opens right now
because it's new but the hello kitty one
so it's pretty cool and then I'll brush
my teeth every day and um yeah then I'll
go into the bathroom and I'll take a
bath or like a shower or whatever huh so
yeah yay shower / bathtub um and if i
have time to you then I kind of prefer
baths a lot because I think bats are
really nice and relaxing and like when
they're warm they're really nice to just
like stay in there for a while so yeah
that's the next thing that I'll do then
after that i'll usually go and pick what
i'm going to wear today this is what I'm
wearing today I'm going to show you
closer this is my outfit that I'm
wearing today it is kind of like a
two-piece dress skirt thing it's like
white there and then it's just like
green with these cool flowers on it and
the coolest thing about this outfit is I
actually have Hello Kitty tights huh I
love hello kitty so I thought they were
so cool it's like my favorite part of
this so the clothes that i have here
right now are like kind of a mess
because been in California the last
couple of months and now i'm back here
in connecticut for a while so the
clothes that i do still have here are
kind of a mess but yeah then i'll
usually picked my outfit so yeah right
now I honestly just have like a lot of
clothes kind of all over the place so
it's kind of a mess and kind of hard to
find stuff sometimes but yeah so the
next thing I do to get ready which is
kind of like feels like the first thing
because it's very important to me is I
do my makeup I'm just going to quickly
do my makeup right now I have a bunch of
nigga tutorial videos too if you guys
want to like check those out when I'm
doing my makeup kind of like I do pretty
much similar thing usually but I like to
like change my eyeshadow colors all kind
of just like depending on when I'm
wearing or what I'm in the mood to put
on my eyes like what I'm in the mood to
wear
yeah I'm just gonna do my make up really
quick
[Music]
I'll also do my hair so what I'll
usually do with my hair I actually
already have it done right now but what
i'll do is i will straighten it so I
have my straightener right there I don't
actually straighten my hair every day
because I do have pretty naturally
straight hair I always liked my hair to
be perfectly straight so if sometimes I
feel like it kind of got a little bit
waves or anything as I was sleeping and
I'll just kind of go through it and
straighten it and make sure it's as
straight as I want it to be and then
after that then I tease my hair a little
bit and I use tresemme freeze this is
the best hairspray ever this one right
here so this is like my favorite
hairspray ever sorry i know i don't have
the cap on that good the caps are
actually always really hard to get on
these so i don't always even put them
back on but yeah this is my favorite
hairspray it's super super good because
it really really keeps your hair in
place and it does a really good job of
making sure if you have like bangs that
they don't like fall apart pretty much
and what I basically do to my hair is
just straight in it tease it and
hairspray it a little bit and then
sometimes lately i've been using couple
products that i'll show you guys but
yeah that's pretty much what I do but if
you want to see exactly how I do it and
more I guess deaths or whatever then I
do have some hair tutorial videos where
I kind of show you guys how i style it
and do all that last time that I got my
hair cut it was by my friend Edward
trico me he's really cool so I have to
make up on my hands right now a little
bit huh he was actually nice enough to
give me these two amazing products so
this is an anti frizz finishing cream
and it's super good it's just kind of
like a cream that you just kind of like
squirt this a little bit if you have any
frizziness in your hair or if you feel
like you just kind of need this to keep
your hair in place then you just kind of
like rub it into your hair a little bit
I get a mirror huh and then yeah like
the whiteness like when you put it on
your hand completely goes away when you
rub it in and it's super good it makes
your hair look really nice it definitely
keeps it in place and gets rid of any
frizziness or any places that you really
want to like keep it in place it does a
really good job of doing that and if you
have any flyaways that way then this
really keeps them like down makes it so
your hair just like stays like I see a
few right now so I'm just gonna like put
that on there a little I done yet you'll
see that like it goes down a lot and
yeah it was a really good job of like
keeping hair that doesn't want to stay
in the right place in the right place so
it's super good and then the next one is
this and this is a blow-dry serum and
this will make your hair look a lot
better it will keep like any frizz down
just like the other one does and then if
you're straightening your hair it
definitely makes you hear a lot shinier
and make sure here locally night and it
makes you feel a lot smoother which is
really good cuz it like will protect
your hair and make your hair really nice
and shiny and I don't have curly hair
but if you do have curly hair it's also
supposed to like team it a lot your
hairs like you leaked early so it's a
useful for that this one is just kind of
like a clear color when you like fun on
your finger and then just kind of like
put in your hair and then you'll notice
your hair is really shiny like when
you're using it when you're
straightening it or when your stead of
trying to get rid of like frizziness or
things like that and huge thank you to
my friends Edward for telling me about
both these products and forgiving them
to me because they're both awesome and
yeah they're called the warren tricomi
style that's the line that they're from
and it's a blow-dry serum and the
anti-frizz finishing cream so yeah these
are both super good and I would really
recommend ease by the way guys I'm not
sure if my wing on my left eye was a bit
off today so if it was that I'm sorry
usually I don't think I have the hardest
time doing a wing some people always
tell me like wow your makeup is so bad
but I don't know I do it every day so I
don't think it's usually too off but
sometimes obviously it can be a little
bit off so hopefully it's not too bad ok
so that is pretty much what I do what
wake up and how I get ready if you guys
enjoyed watching this video so make sure
you give it a thumbs up so I know that
you liked it and subscribe to my youtube
channel if you want to see more videos
for me also if you want to be notified
whenever I post new videos then you can
click on the bell icon and then you
should know whenever I post I love you
guys I'll see you guys in my next video
bye
[Music]