Superhero Time
Oh no there's a fire in the garden
Can Spiderman put it out?
Ffffffiiiirrrreeee!
Ah ha!
A hose.
Maybe Spiderman could use that?
Nice
Time for a bath fire
Spiderman cannot put out the fire
What will he do?
Hmm, who's this?
Hi
Yeah, cool toy Joker, whatever!
Watch this Spiderman
Up Up Up
Time to put out the fire!
Magic finger
Squirt, squirt, squirt
Ohh, poor fire
Too late Spiderman
What, what where did it go? ohh Joker!
I did it!
Joker 1 Spiderman 0
Spiderman is thirsty after fighting the fire
Yummy
Whoops I need a cup
Hello, I'm back
Shh be very quiet
I'll take that
Shake it, shake it, shake it
Poor Spiderman
He won't know what hit him
So so funny, enjoy it Spiderman
Now which one should I drink?
Should I drink the Coke?
Yum
Or should I drink the Pepsi?
You tell me
Up there in the corner, press the button and
cast your vote
Coke or Pepsi, which one?
I think I'll drink the Coke
Actually I'll change, I think I might go the
Pepsi
Oh no the Coke I love Coke
Or no I love Pepsi
So so funny
Joker has done it again
Poor Spiderman
bye bye
Hello
Hello Spiderman
Hey Spidergirl
Come inside I have a little surprise
What is it?
So I've got a new pet, can you guess what
it is?
Roar, a dinosaur?
No, it's not a dinosaur.
Wait here
Spidergirl runs outside to get her new pet
Come on Sammy, come with me
This is my skeleton, Sammy.
Sammy the skeleton.
Sammy skeleton
oh Hi, Wow!
You have a pet skeleton?
He copies what you say, watch
I'm a clever skeleton
Hello Sammy, hello Sammy
Hello Sammy
I'm a silly skeleton
I'm going to get a snack, do you want something?
I think I'll play with Sammy
Boo
Hello
Sammy, oh Sammy, you're funny
Spidergirl!
You guys
You are a silly skeleton
Spiderman, Coke and the Bad Baby Joker
Superhero Time
It's a hot sunny day and Spiderman is very
thirsty
A drink!
Oh it's empty!
Spiderman really needs a drink, when suddenly..
Yes!
Ice Cold Coke!
Hello Spiderman, how can I help you today?
One of these Coke's thanks Hulk
Here you go, Ice cold Coke, enjoy.
That'll be $3 thanks
1, 2, 3.
Thank you very much Spiderman.
Enjoy your Coke
Delicious.
Oh but I'm still thirsty and I haven't got
any money.
Spiderman needs to ask Hulk a favour.
Another drink.
But Hulk is not there.
Thanks Hulk.
Hey, my Coke, there's one missing.
Spiderman.
Hulk is very angry!
I'm going to get that Spiderman, but I need
some help.
Hello Hulk.
Need some help?
The Bad Baby Joker!
Go, get Spiderman!
Spiderman, Spiderman, where are you?
I'll take that!
MMm Coke, my favorite!
Oh yum, it makes me crazy!
Hey that's mine!
Catch me if you can Spiderman!
You can't get me!
Let go of me!
I got ya!
Take that Spiderman.
Don't you take my Coke!
Bye bye!
Hi kids, if you like this video please like
and subscribe down below, also leave a comment
and tell us what you want to see next on Superhero
Time!
Thanks for watching, bye!