what's up guys so what's happening great
eugenia cooney made a response video to
me and well it wasn't really a response
but it was her on you now as usual that
and more on today's own easy on speaks
okay hi hello I'm not Mitchell Davis
someone named Jamie submitted this to me
by email so I guess it's my duty to
watch what you genius said about me as
I've repeatedly indicated that I care
first we'll check out the comments you
can tell she's lying I honestly love
Eugenia but she's gotten really skinny
and every time I see her I feel fat and
I can't help to think that I should
starve myself Wow okay so the first
comment somewhat admitting that Eugenia
triggers them just like I've repeatedly
said Eugenia does and the reason I said
that is because the countless people who
have come to me saying hey Eugenia is
triggering me thank you for making your
videos trying to educate people on
anorexia and how serious it is but I'm
not be essing here that literally is the
first comet that showed us princezz the
rounded off shape of her teeth is a
common symptom from people with bulimia
I won't sit on her channel and harass
her but I have no doubt in my mind she's
dealing with something and here they say
people need to leave her alone she's
human just like the rest of us a nice
Tiana has no right to say these things
about Eugenia and her weight for health
is her business I assume that caring
about her and asking questions is fine
but you just said it's none of our
business don't contradict yourself
anyway you go on to say but don't harass
her and assume she has an eating
disorder simply because she seems
skinnier than most okay guys hold on
it's not that she's skinnier than most
it's that she's dying you understand
that right here's someone saying this is
naturally skinny I eat three meals a day
I'm 56 and I'm so disgusted thank you an
easy on for speaking the truth there's
another person that says this is what
naturally skinny looks like I agree with
you that Eugene Shakuni is sick she
needs hel person says this is message to
you in Eugenia I am 14 127 pounds and I
am naturally skinny show this to her
okay so we know what naturally skinny is
but for the sake of emphasizing my
points let's go ahead and also check out
google results this is the first thing
is show up for naturally skinny
ectomorph obviously being an example and
here's another example of naturally
skinny again I'm not cherry-picking so
there you go let's check out Eugenia
Cooney here's one example does that look
natural to you another example does that
look natural to you now this video was
uploaded January 29th to her channel
take a look at her legs okay you see her
legs now look at my arm which has a
greater girth my arm or Eugenia cooney's
freaking leg even if you Gina Cooney's
upper leg is thicker than this the fact
that it's even close is insane
we disturb it before I continue let me
be clear about why I'm making these
videos one Eugenia Cooney obviously
needs help too she's irrefutably
triggering people to starve themselves
which could lead to death statistically
and three these videos do very well so
obviously there's enough people to care
about this to make it worth talking
about this is called full transparency
you guys and the people who say her
health is her business yes it is her
business until she starts to kill
herself and she publicly displays that
she's killing herself and it's every
caring person's duty to take care of her
ie encouraging a large audience to go to
her and send her messages that encourage
her to eat again so she can save her own
life ignoring the issue will not solve
the issue I think most any logical
person who understands the definition of
stagnation was that stagnation or what
you're encouraging is the enemy of
progress but let's see what biceps four
legs had to say in response since then
he really hasn't liked me too much like
you keeps accusing me of all this stuff
and I'm influencing people on all this
stuff and so many videos i've used
factual literal examples of people
saying they're starving themselves
because of you you Gina you need to
address this fat you need to stop making
your outfit videos where you do your
little spin showing off your inner xik
body because that is what you literally
have there's no way you're that
naturally skinny and most any doctor
would agree and I say most any doctor
would agree because you actually having
a condition that makes your body that
way is statistically highly improbable
now a young American white girl who
starves herself that is statistically
far more likely I'm simply using readily
available data calculate whether or not
you're honest and the conclusion based
on your behavior and that data it's not
looking good for you Eugenia like I
don't even know why he was looking at my
Twitter to be honest I know he said in
his videos because he was like checking
in with me I looked at your Twitter
because you hadn't uploaded a video in
five days and I was worried that you
might be in the hospital or something
I'm not making videos like promoting my
body you're not making videos promoting
your body all right let's check out a
video you've made recently this is
called winter outfits video published
January 29 2017 ginia literally just
says that she doesn't make videos
promoting her body and as you're about
to see that is a blatant lie I don't
know so here's a nice oh my god oh how
do your legs not snap
no I think Marcus people do that while
sitting with the ceiling yes sitting
video game so the majority of the skin
above your waist is showing nearly
advertising your flesh and you can
clearly see your legs below your waist
which is again obviously showing off how
skinny you are hence why so many girls
come to me saying that you trigger them
what do you trigger them to do starve
themselves and in one out of every five
cases of anorexia kill themselves
alright so here's hoping that was the
only lie in your broadcast be making
something like an outfit video is not me
promoting my body it's just me showing
outfit let's say you make a video of you
baking a cake and putting that cake on
display in a video for you to say I'm
not showing off the cake I'm just
showing off the frosting is extremely
illogical and you are taking your entire
human body putting it in a skimpy outfit
and spinning it on camera that is you
not only showing off your outfit but
that is you showing off your body
otherwise you could simply hold them up
in front of the camera like you've done
before and say this is my new outfit but
I'm not gonna show off my anorexic body
because that would trigger a lot of
girls watching my videos he says he's
not gonna make these videos anymore that
is cool I would give him a chance like
great what I literally said was that i'm
resigning from making those videos
literally resigning but i am officially
resigning from the topic and when i
checked up on you months later to see
that you're still starving yourself I
felt a little compelled to again discuss
the issue that literally millions of
people care about eugenia those millions
of people care about you believe it or
not those millions of people no doubt
want you to get better I don't know how
many times people have to say you are
triggering young girls to starve
themselves and that you need to take
better care of yourself before you
actually register and you're starved
brain that you should maybe actually
listens to these hundreds of thousands
of people who are screaming for you to
get better if someone tries to give you
a helping hand don't slap their hand
away ask yourself why they're giving you
this helping hand in literally the
hundreds of thousands so let him get you
down oh thank you Clem fairy yes thank
you an abler don't let this guy telling
you to take better care of your body get
you down internet logic um and I mean
it's fine I mean he can make videos
about whatever he wants i guess but it
just kind of sucks because then he
starts like accusing me of all this
stuff it is a charger claim that someone
has done something illegal or wrong
not just an accusation eugenia let me
give you some examples this one this one
this one this one this one this one this
one this one this one
[Music]
[Applause]
am i clear enough do you understand that
you are literally triggering people to
kill themselves do you understand that
take some responsibility for your own
actions but ya know it just kind of
sucks cuz then like he starts like
accusing me of like all this stuff and
then it also like turns all these other
people against me guess what people were
against you way before I ever talked
about you Eugenia you have been
promoting you're starved body for years
and you have been getting dislikes for
years let me show you what I mean the
ice bucket challenge video a video you
made way before I ever made a video
talking about sickly you are which by
the way guys look at her legs you see
how much more healthy her legs look back
then even though they still look sickly
do you not see how much better they look
this is literal proof that Eugene had
literally been starving herself
regardless even at that waits people
were disliking her videos in hordes and
a comment from a year ago points out
that the video is related to your video
show up as dealing with anorexia when
your video has nothing to do with
anorexia that's a freakin sign from
YouTube itself Eugenia there's another
person from a year ago implying that she
needs a KFC bucket challenge aka that
she should eat more someone from a year
ago saying you could drive a truck
through her thigh gap 622 likes against
was not inspired by any video I made you
clearly got this on your own Eugenia so
don't blame any criticism you get on me
because blaming me won't make you gain
weight blaming me won't make you more
healthy blaming me is the easy way out
to avoid having to take responsibility
for what you're doing to yourself but
again Eugenia this is your body two
years ago and this is your body from a
video uploaded februari 12 2017 now if
you look at these side by side and you
tell me she's not starving herself I'm
gonna ask you what does she have AIDS
because she must have contracted some
serious disease to lose that much body
mass and have it not be her fault it
must be a disease when you see what has
this like done this kind of stuff with
like a lot of people really I've made
videos about youtubers starving
themselves actually no I can't think of
a single video using a youtubers name in
the title saying they starve themselves
because out of a thousands of videos
I've made I do not recall a single one
that's like that so it looks like that's
blatant lie number two from Eugenia I
really don't think he's just doing it
because he's like worried you're right
I'm not doing it just because I'm
worried I've stated this multiple times
in the past 1i am worried about you I
don't want you to die prematurely too
I'm worried about your audience the
people you're triggering
[Music]
based on the evidence I've displayed in
this video and many other videos and
three a lot of people care about this
issue and myself trying to reach a wider
audience it only makes sense for me to
make videos like this so there you go
Eugenia that's called the full truth and
nothing but the truth you should try it
sometime I mean I think he does it
because he likes to try to get like
views and attention on himself literally
every youtuber likes to get views in
attention eugenia guess what that
applies to you too cuz we both know that
if you got on you now and nobody watched
you probably would not participate in
you now ever again because you didn't
get the attention you wanted translation
you like attention just like every other
youtuber to present that so
hypocritically as if it doesn't apply to
you as well it's just more dishonesty I
kind of feel like he already has a lot
of like mistakes that he's made and a
lot of like not-so-great things that
he's done so that's your tactic try to
distract people from the fact that
you're actively starving herself by
pointing out that I've made mistakes in
the past but I'm not continuing to make
so if anyone who's not a hundred percent
perfect criticizes you they must be
invalid well to my knowledge there's not
a single perfect human being on this
earth who's not a literal baby and they
can't even speak English so they can't
criticize you conclusion nobody can
criticize eugenia cooney because we're
all imperfect that's a great way to go
on starving yourself avoiding the real
problem at hand so the fact that he kind
of like keeps like pointing out what he
thinks is like wrong with everyone else
and trying to make everyone else into
the bad one I'm not trying to make
everyone else into the bad one eugenia
haven't called out a single other
youtuber for clearly triggering their
audience into starving themselves what
will it take for you just to admit that
you're wrong is that even possible why
is it you do not understand the damage
you do every single time you release a
video triggering your audience to star
themselves as a result of you clearly
showing off your body he was fat shaming
Trisha Paytas oh my gosh that's so
messed up I was fat shaming Trisha
Paytas are you talking about me
comparing her to Fiona because one I
said that for the sake of comedy and two
I said that for the sake of comedy and
three I said that for the sake of comedy
and four I said that for the sake of
comedy as a comedian recognized by
millions not sure what you expect when
you go to a standard stand-up special
hey you guys it's dane cook and today
we're gonna make fun of no one
hahaha nobody's gonna get made fun of
today so my first joke you know how when
you're walking across the street and oh
wait somebody has to walk across the
street and you're probably gonna wind up
making fun of that person crossing the
street you know what next joke okay so
here we go all right dane cook here you
know how when you're eating food and
shit now we've got to make fun of the
person eating food well guess i gotta be
a veterinarian all right moving on oh
wait that's the thing with an easy on
it's like he kind of like tears apart
everyone I literally don't make videos
about everyone I haven't publicly
criticized Tiffany Joe Allen I haven't
publicly criticized makemebad 35 I
haven't publicly criticized Billy the
fridge although I did do a comedy video
where's cracking jokes about him is that
allowed you Gina am I allowed to tell
jokes if he thinks like you're too
skinny then who keep fixing you for that
but then if he thinks you're like two
big rig is like doing then he does that
that's how normal humans function like
if there's a girl who's 55 and weighs
250 she probably weighs too much she's
55 and 180 well I don't see a problem
with that probably cuz the person who's
180 is likely going to have a long
healthy life now a girl like you Eugenia
who's 59 and about 60-something pounds
maybe 70 at most yeah there's like a
twenty-five percent chance that you're
gonna die about Eugenia you're killing
yourself and you're acting like I'm the
bad guy wake up please I just don't get
why he needs to like judge everyone so
much am i judging i just seen for her
wait am i judging jenna Marbles for her
weights am i judging zoella for her
weight am i judging kal-el kitten for
her weights am i judging hannah minx for
her weight i may be commented on three
female youtubers out of the hundreds of
female youtubers regarding their weight
so i really hope you'll stop lying to
your audience implying that i do this to
everyone when it is a fact that i do not
he's dumb as act like thanks Kaylee yeah
and it's like I'm not raised like name
call hammer get like you guys to go
ahead and him or anything like that he's
dumb as f thanks yeah and I'm not trying
to say he's dumb as f or hate on him
like I literally just did ginia if
you're gonna dislike someone own it if
you're gonna like someone own it don't
say thanks for calling own easy on dumb
as fuck and then pretend to be innocent
it is so dishonest to do that I don't
know I just like really just do not see
the point of him doing it to encourage
you to save your own life inspire the
many individuals who have been triggered
by watching your videos to start eating
healthy as well no I don't see the
point in me promoting a healthier
lifestyle and potentially saving
hundreds if not thousands of people from
killing themselves through starvation I
don't see the point in that that's your
genius logic all right why is he even
like still doing this okay I'll say it
again because I want you to become more
healthy because I want the people you've
triggered to become more healthy and I
want to make content that's relevant to
my audience interests I have said this
so many times in my previous videos but
it's almost like you don't pay attention
whatsoever in fact eugenia if you could
make a response video I don't care on
what channel you do it you can do it on
a channel with no subscribers make a
response video to this video addressing
my every single point and then I might
be able to respect your position but so
far it seems like you're just trying to
plug your ears and close your eyes and
pretend reality doesn't exist it does
Eugenia and you have a lot to answer for
like maybe he's I didn't think he was
really gonna do that because like I know
he said that he's not gonna make drama
videos anymore said I wasn't going to
share new private information about my
relationships behind-the-scenes
information that is negative I said I
wasn't going to publicly bash
ex-girlfriends X friends and future
videos I did not however say that I will
never make a video again about people
who starve themselves and trigger young
girls like them to starve themselves as
well it's not some typical drama video
this isn't even a hate video I haven't
been sitting here calling you names
other than names based on fact like you
being dishonest you keep trying to
strawman your way out of this by
distracting people to unrelated issues
by submitting points that aren't
relevant to what we're actually talking
about and acting like that resolves it
but it's time for you to stand still
look forward and face the real issue and
I noted he also said that like his last
video is like his final video or
whatever again in that video I literally
said I was resigning from the topic but
I am officially resigning from the topic
last time I checked when you resign from
something you can take it up again if
you choose and that's exactly what I did
so long story short Eugenia I hope you
actually do watch this video I hope even
more you make a response video on some
totally irrelevant channel that nobody
cares about so you can avoid me getting
promoted based on it but at least
finally address the issues at hand
because nowhere did you prove that
you're not triggering young girls to
starve themselves nowhere did you prove
that you're finally eating a healthy
diet no where did you prove that you're
not actively killing yourself in general
and overall you didn't really prove any
of my points wrong we're talking about
mortality here eugenia if you don't have
your life you don't have anything and
your life is
what I'm literally trying to say i'm
also trying to save the lives of people
you've triggered with your clearly
irrefutably triggering videos now the
fact that you try to turn what I'm doing
into something hateful is it expected
response because growing as a human
being can be very difficult and human
beings tend to take the convenient route
rather than the one that takes effort
but you said it yourself that I can make
videos about whatever I want and so if I
continue to feel compelled about making
videos regarding people who are actively
killing themselves and I believe I am
within my rights because as I said
before Eugenia I like you better living
but you are showing a level of denial
that is typical and people with anorexia
so I can't say this video will help you
beyond the fact that it'll generate you
even more subscribers so for that you're
welcome and to everyone else if you have
ideas on how we can help Eugenia Cooney
and her audience please email me my
email is listed on my youtube channel
thank you