hey guys if u jeediyey today is going to
be doing a kind of like Valentine's Day
themed video because it's actually like
febuary now well actually in the data of
building this is technically in January
their dessert so but if n putting this
alex is probably going to already be
febuary it's like the perfect time to do
this oh my your hair like a little bit
different areas i'm not sure i don't
really have like that much hair spray in
it right now i actually got it done a
little bit earlier and the girls dude is
super super good job I'm not curious now
it's like a little bit later in the day
and I haven't Legree straighten or
anything it's kind of like coming apart
I hope not because yeah I thought she
did such a good job so I didn't really
want to like mess with it too much so
yeah anyways I thought in this video
since it's like Valentine's Day months
and stuff hi I would just do some kind
of like dating like the relationship
love kind of advice so yeah that's what
this video is going to be about I know
it haven't really been in too many
relationships other than was like Jack
Skellington but hey I'm going to like
give you guys some advice anyway and
like see how this goes I definitely one
thing that I would say it's really
really important like no matter who it
is that you're interested in or who it
is that you might be doing or someone
that you want to date or just like
whatever is that I think the thing that
is super super important is to always be
yourself and never feel like you have to
change yourself for anybody and I really
feel like that just applies to a lot of
things whether it's the way that you act
or the way that you look whatever I
really think it's important you guys to
remember that you guys are all very very
special people and you guys are all
super unique you might not like realize
that sometimes I know all the time the
world tries to bring people down
unfortunately you should never wish that
you or anyone else other than yourself
like there's only one of you and they'll
never be anyone who is exactly like you
so I think that's very important thing
to remember if somebody doesn't accept
you as you are whether it's like the way
that you look or something about your
personality or just like whatever then I
really feel like it's really important
for you guys to know that you should
never feel like you have 14 I mean
unless you're doing really bad things or
alert
upsetting people or doing things that
are actually legit bad to people that i
always think it is good to try some like
improve yourself and try to delete the
best version of yourself that you can be
I don't feel like it's really important
to be a good person and to try to make
people happy but don't ever feel like I
need to change who you are if you think
that you don't want to do to change
things about the way you look or
whatever because if you're like having
to be someone else that person's ever
you like or whatever even if they just
like you or whatever it would it really
be truly liking you because you want
somebody to truly love who you are for
the beautiful person that you are so I
think it's really important to remember
to be yourself and you're single right
now in Valentine's Day or just whatever
this remembers that's totally okay i
just think ill to to like it's okay
we're single together I just get my
relationships like on weed out but now
you now got rid of the proposals are you
so now we can't even get relationships
on there it's super depressing but I
just think it's really important to
remember the guys that even if like
you're single right now it really is
okay and you really don't need someone
your life to be happy I do lots of other
people too like whether it is like
friends or pets or whatever there's so
many like great people there for you to
love and people that love you so just
remember to even if you're single right
now they're on Valentine's Day it really
doesn't matter you're gone and think
it's really this day it's really about
that because you have felt so bad for
being single it's okay to be single and
single two so we are like single friends
but you are reading someone or if there
is someone that you're interested in or
really just two more people in general I
feel like this is very important thing
to do in life this is generally how do
we think it's very important in life to
show people that you care about them and
to tell them that you love them and just
to do nice things for people i joined is
just a super super important thing in
life like you can make people so happy
by doing nice things for them and just
like shooting people right and trying to
be a good person or instead you could
really bring people down by not being so
nice and saying some not-so-nice things
or
just like things like that in general so
I always feel like it's a really
important things we tried to be a nice
person and just to show people that you
do care about them and you tell people
that you loved it and this will
hopefully not be happening to anyone
like right now or anything but like if
that person wasn't see around win big
you know knew it at least feel really
good if you were to tell that person
right now that you love them and that
you care for them and that's why it's
really always important to show people
that and she's like express your love
for people and for things in your life
that you're grateful for i also just
think it's a really good thing in
general to just try to be a good
Christian life like I know a lot of
people on the internet really do not
like me and I am sorry to dispute but we
don't like me but I really always do try
to be a good Christian and to make
people happy I mean feel like that's a
good thing to you guys because that way
you'll be attracting people into your
life who are also trying to be positive
towards people and make people happy I
really feel like as people are just like
judging you being negative and not being
nice to you then those aren't any people
that you want in your life anyway so I
really feel like it's just important if
you try to be a good person to reach
everyone to be nice to people and that
way you'll attract people into your life
to actually like should be there it was
like the right people in your life
remember if there's lots of ways to meet
people and fast like even if you feel
really lonely right now there's tons of
people out there in the world and when I
asked for fighting chance or creating
you're just like whatever yeah I know
where it's a really big world up there
and there's so many great people out
there I really believe that everything
does happen for a reason and a lot of
the time to write people just like find
their way into your life like you just
have to see what happens and just try to
stay positive even one that's hard and
remember things can get better to let
the internet even though there's some
really not so nice people on the
internet there's so many great and nice
people on the internet
literally I wouldn't notice so many
great people that I do know now if it
wasn't for you internet so remember you
can always be people online and there's
tons of great ways to meet people in the
world I'm not everything the people that
you're interested in or even people you
just want to be friends with or just
like whatever it I really think it's
cool like when people try to take
interesting things that that person is
interested in you guys could find common
and chest that you guys are both into
you and I think that's a really great
way to have a conversation just like to
talk about things so it feels like
something that someone that you like is
really interested in I think it's a
really cool thing to actually try to
like the interested in that too and not
just only five interest the things that
you're already interested in its all I
am saying like to like pretend to like
what that person is liking it might be a
thing in the world that you actually
didn't even know you were super
interested in yet and you don't gives
new things a chance then you'll never
know that I'm feeling it's cool to take
intro and things that other people are
also interested in and in that way you
guys can kind of find things that you're
both commonly interested in and then
it's a good way to like fall to people
and makes the relationship I really
think I should Valentine's Day coming up
I know they just think it's a very good
thing to remember that even if you're
single or if you are in a relationship
or just whatever just like remember the
important people in your life that you
do care about and even if you feel like
there's like nobody right now I'm you
feel really alone because I know
sometimes it can be really easily to
feel like lonely and feel very alone in
the world but just remember there is
seriously always people out there that
care about you I care about you and a
lot of people you care about you just
always remember that and trying to stay
as positive as you can I really hope
that you guys enjoyed this video if you
did to make sure that you give it a
thumbs up so I know that you liked it
also subscribe to my youtube channel if
you like snow and I put civilians
because i miss new videos a lot also if
you'd like to you can actually press the
bell icon and then you'll be notified
whenever I post a new video and yeah all
right I said you know
unless i'll see you in my next video
okay five
[Music]
bye