hey guys it's Eugenia so today I'm going
to be doing a story time video where I'm
going to be telling you guys something
pretty crazy that happened to me so yeah
by the way guys also I actually got a
haircut today so if my hair looks any
different than a totally why when I very
cut my hair I don't really cut it very
much because I like I'm here to be
pretty wall but yeah I got a haircut
today so it's another thing I did so
basically today though before i even
went to get my hair done i was actually
at the police department because i had
to go in there because of what happened
pretty much so as you can see by the
title of this video this sounds like
it's a pretty crazy thing that happened
so a week ago if you guys didn't know I
was actually in Disney World I know
probably some of you guys might think
it's really weird that i've been disney
was so often but my brother is like
really really into disney so that's why
I'm there I'd a lot but yeah I was there
and then I randomly got this phone call
because I'm being on the internet like
there's a lot of really good things to
come from the internet and I really
loved getting to make videos for you
guys but also online sometimes some
really really bad not-so-great things
can happen like I had to really like
weird things like kind of done to me and
things that have happened from being
online like I've had like SWAT team sent
to my house I've had a weird letters and
things like that sense in my house I've
had people kind of be able to like spy
on me on my computer and I've had
hackers which is really really not fun
so yeah just like a lot of stuff so yeah
so this day I was getting a phone call
from a number that I did it really
recognized sometimes like another thing
that will happen to me is I'll get a lot
of like phone calls from unknown numbers
and then when I answer them it just
turns out that like the person won't
tell me who they are and they just kind
of don't say anything so that's like
another thing that I guess happens from
being online sometimes yeah I answered
it and it turned out that they told me
that they were actually the police with
one of those like weird kind of thing
that happened a couple of years ago when
I actually got swatted it was like this
whole super super crazy thing like it
was this probably onion to guy and he
started telling me all this crazy stuff
and all this stuff he was gonna do to me
and I was gonna send the SWAT team to my
house but I think he would actually do
it because at the time I really didn't
know anything about swatting I didn't
even know I knew it was a thing or how
it worked for anything like that but it
turned out he was kind of telling the
truth at least with that part he also
said he was gonna send like drugs to my
house and called the drug administration
or he never did that which is police
good but yeah like he sent a whole slots
into my house and my door here is
actually still broken from that day so
yeah it was pretty bad course like when
all that was going on it ended up being
some like kid in Canada of course the
police kind of had to get involved cuz
they had alike send out the SWAT team
and it was crazy so I was thinking when
I got this phone call from the police I
was a little bit scared not like to
scared but I was kind of like why would
the police keep calling me cuz I'm
really a person I don't try to do
anything wrong I don't try to break the
law or to do anything super bad like
killing people or doing bad things so I
was likewise with the police be calling
me they told me that they wanted me to
go into their police department I was
like yeah I could do that I'm actually
waiting Disney right now but when i get
back then yeah they were totally cool
with that they were really nice and that
when I was kind of thinking it over
later I was just thinking like okay like
why would the police want me to go into
their office it must maybe be related to
onion like maybe it's because they have
like a court case with him they want me
to answer questions I don't know it must
be something like that because I didn't
think they would be like a reason that
like I would have to go to the police so
it turns out that now as you can see
like by all my stuff here I'm back from
Disney now so today was actually the day
that I went into the police department
like I gave them a phone call back like
I said
and I went in today but literally just
expecting it to me about that we even
talked about that a little bit and then
they told me the reason that I was being
called in so it turns out I'm not
exactly sure about like why this
happened or what was going on for what
exactly so I actually weren't this today
and I guess there's this like online
cyber tip kind of thing and it's
actually really good thing so I guess a
lot of people tip like for child
pornography which I would of course
never do because I think that stuff is
really messed up guys oops i just
realized my two necklaces alike in my
sweater so taking those up now and i
don't even really know how that works I
don't know people tip if they like know
someone who's doing that or is like kids
reach out and then try to get whoever is
like forcing them to do pictures or I
don't know exactly how any of that works
like I don't know anything about child
pornography think it's a really bad
thing so it's a really good thing that
that does exist so things like that can
stop but yeah I guess you've Oh could
also to other stuff too so I guess
somebody like less than the tip saying
that I am actually kidnapped and it's
yeah it gets like really really weird so
I guess my fate it was that when I was
15 my parents actually kidnapped me and
they've been brainwashing me ever since
then I think it's like blue eating
through my parents but also he said that
I was like how old hostage against my
will and yeah it was all just so crazy
to me I just like what cuz I mean unless
I like brainwashed and I don't know
what's going on then I was definitely
not kidnapped her brainwashed by my
parents like it was just like wow that
is insane like that is probably learned
a Kree
things I've ever heard also apparently
from what the police was telling me the
person who like left than the message
was like legitimately concerns that I
was being like held hostage and if the
person really was then um person thank
you very much for caring about me I
really appreciate that if I ever were to
be kidnapped or something like that that
you would care enough to try to get me
like I'm kidnapped but yeah I'm
definitely not kidnapped and definitely
not being like held hostage for anything
crazy like that but thank you person for
care it sets what their intentions work
another thing guys if he didn't actually
notice about me when I was born my name
is actually not even Eugenia it was
actually calling for a couple of days
because I guess my parents didn't really
know exactly what they wanted to name me
so getting me Colleen at first but then
in a couple of days I became Eugenia the
person actually like even wrote in it
was really crazy because they wanted me
to bring in my birth certificate when I
was going to the police station let's
talk him to my mom about that too and
she was kind of like um you probably
feel so bring your name change forms
because otherwise they might be confused
if they are looking at your birth
certificate because your birth
certificate so says Colleen because my
birth certificate actually still says
calling so um yeah then it was really
weird because in like the tip it was
like a whole paragraph that they wrote
to deploy ease they said that my name
was really calling Schwartz and it was
just really rude to me because my name
was originally Colleen I have no idea
we're thinking about with the whole
Schwartz thing I don't think I was ever
calling Schwartz like I definitely was
not ever calling short I do have a
middle name that begins with an S but
it's definitely not Schwartz it was kind
of crazy because then the police
actually asked me if I was into bondage
and I was just kind of like no I don't
really think it's a bondage or anything
and I also asked me if my mom was into
bondage and as far as I know
think my mom is such like nope she's not
doing that then you're like yeah we know
this is like a really awkward question
to be asking you about that but then
they said like I guess this person who
sent this in was writing some luck thing
like I guess they were saying like oh ki
chidiya won't do a mukbang I don't
exactly know how that happened but they
mentioned among thing I guess the police
doesn't really know what a muck thing is
so they thought it might've been some
like fetish thing because I don't know
the first had meant to do is a fetish
thing like I think no really I know what
I'm up paying this guy is and I know so
you will do for whatever reason really
want me to do this but I don't really do
videos like that so yeah I just like
feel like it's kind of awkward for me to
do those videos but um anyways thing out
of the person like bench and net so so
yeah it's just like really looks like
awkward yeah me and my mom we don't we
don't like post bondage videos or
anything like that but yeah they said
they just like had to ask me that and
they kind of asked me a couple of other
questions they asked me some questions
from youtubers that have also been
videos with me sitting the personal
cemented a couple of them and I guess
the first had also mentioned marina
Joyce I not exactly sure why maybe
because I know she had like a lot of
kidnapping rumors and hers are way more
extreme than mine fine was just kind of
his one person I'm really glad that
marina wasn't kidnapped though because
she's really awesome and she seems
really really nice so I'm really happy
that she was not too kidnapped huh it's
just really crazy to me though that
people like report people as being
kidnapped when they're not kidnapped but
um I do appreciate it the person thought
I really was kidnapped or anything like
that because I guess they were trying to
get me like staves or unconnect but yeah
I'm definitely not kidnapped so it was
just really crazy to me but yeah it was
just such a crazy thing to be because
when I went into the police today that
was definitely not at all what I was
expecting they said they just kind of
had to call me in there just to make
sure everything was
okay they just gonna ask you a couple
more questions just kind of like related
to all this and um yeah I guess they
said they just gonna have to do that but
in someone reports the stuff because
it's a pretty like big thing to be
reporting obviously so yeah that's
pretty much for happen but the police is
really really nice they were really nice
about this whole situation I just
thought it was a really really crazy
story though so thought i would share
just with you guys and yeah person for
whoever for whatever reason thanks to
kidnap to see you know i am definitely
not kidnapped and definitely not being
held hostage by my parents or anything
like that so definitely my real pirates
too I mean unless I really am being
brainwashed and I'm just completely
unaware of this but I bet that that is
totally not the case so yeah I
definitely don't think I brainwashed or
anything crazy like that or being
kidnapped you're held hostage I guess
that that is my story it's pretty crazy
so if you guys enjoyed this video though
or you liked watching me talk about this
crazy thing that happened then make sure
you give this video a like so I know
that you liked it also subscribe to my
youtube channel if you want to know what
I post the videos because i post new
videos a lot also make sure that you
click on the little bell notification
because that way when I posting videos
you'll always be notified so you'll know
what I post and let me know if you guys
like this video maybe I'll do more kind
of story videos if you guys liked this
video if I think of like other
interesting things to share with you
guys well I love you guys so much and
I'll see you guys in my next video all
right bye