you see it every day when you look at
the clock read the labels in your
breakfast cereal watch your favorite TV
show check your social media see an
advertisement or even by watching this
video we are all too familiar with
design but ever wonder why what makes a
good design what makes it attractive
what makes it likely what makes a good
design work it turns out there's a
science behind it there are a lot of
principles that designers obey or
sometimes creatively disobey to create a
good design one principle designers use
is dis talk theory on the Year eighteen
ninety is tall is a term coined by
Austin philosopher christian von erin
fells but it will be until nineteen
twenties when the prominent founders max
why flirt wolf in cooler and curved
Kostka created the principles it
describes the science and how do we
perceive things visually especially when
the parts relate to the cool and modern
day turn this top means figure form
shape and structure today its
application radiance from problem
solving psychology therapy and
especially on visual design you saw fear
when a fine to visual designs has six
main principles first similarity
principle it happens what objects look
similar to one another viewers will
often see individual elements as part of
a pattern or group this effect can be
used to create single illustration image
or message from a series of separate
elements next there is common fate or
continually we perceive moving objects
in the scene directions as related to
each other more so than the elements
that are stationary or appear to be
moving in the different direction then
closure
this works when an object is incomplete
or the interior space of an element is
not fully closed but the viewer
perceives a complete shape by filling
out the missing information proximity
uses the closed arrangement or distance
of elements to create a group
association between those objects if
individual elements are also similar
they will tend to be perceived as a
single cool even though they are
separate elements next is pronounced
meaning figure and brown it often uses
the idea of light and shade to help
create an image that jumps out from the
series of shapes lastly symmetry as you
probably know we perceive objects are
made out of two complementary halves
this is where balance and harmony all of
these gestalt principles are
scientifically studied ways on how we
perceive visually designers use or
totally disregard this principle in
order to make their design unique but as
we all know being unique might sometimes
be quirky or uncool nevertheless the
next time you see a design see how many
principles can you spot and appreciate
the word behind a good design