Did you know that every person has a unique tongue print?
Zero Lies, Full Facts This is FUFA.
We all know about footprints and fingerprints.
But guess what, all of us have unique tongue prints as well.
Besides, it is the only body part that can
protrude out
and settle right back inside comfortably in your mouth.
Now there is research being conducted to use the tongue as a reliable id proof;
which means that in the near future you need to be careful
while you are mocking someone by sticking your tongue out.Who knows?
You might just be giving away your password.
For more such unknown facts like,share, subscribe and ofcourse comment us in the comment section