so the whole point of it is ping beam
Allah Allah give him a million and once
I have said that that it's really a
lifestyle change
hey there today we are going to feature
a ten step guide to losing weight based
on a compilation of tips from no less
than miss sharon cuneta if you haven't
subscribed yet - Chatta Mary TV please
subscribe for more inspiring videos like
this here Sharon step number one pad
thai or whatever I want to eat haunted I
don't fit in I don't know no carbs on
Instagram Sharon gave this step to one
of her followers she said in the
beginning if you're serious
cut out all cards rice bread pasta
potatoes punch it just have regular
violence but only eat a very small
amount number 4 chew slowly
number five keep it up
she kept telling herself Sharon just six
months out of your life and the rest of
your years will be happier than now it's
been two years and she still keeps
telling herself that she has 20 to lose
she said I have dropped around 75 I keep
saying I have 20 to lose after I lose
the 20 I will probably still be saying I
have to lose 20
[Music]
number seven do not think of the few
months ahead instead just do it day by
day
[Music]
number eight number nine try to avoid
fried foods instead go for grilled or
steamed number ten use stevia instead of
sugar
according to stevia calm the stevia
plant is a small shrub that has been
used as a sweetener for hundreds of
years the stevia leaf extract is a
highly potent natural sweetener that can
be anywhere from two hundred to three
hundred fifty times sweeter than sugar
this alternative to sugar is known to
have zero calories so these are the ten
very useful and effective steps the
cheran followed as her guide to losing
weight but overall this is what Sharon
wants to point out well the whole point
of it is
hing be malevolent and Athene and one
can accept that that it's really a
lifestyle change one of Sharon's
followers on Instagram posted this
comment and Sharons reply somehow sums
up her 10 step guide on how to lose
weight
[Music]
last February 12 Sharron posted an
inspiring message on her Facebook page
wherein she looked back to January 2016
when this was how she looked and then
she made a vow to herself she said I
would not stop until I looked in the
mirror and saw the real me again because
these first two pictures never where and
then she posted four more photos of her
this time they were taken just this year
which was two years after she started
changing her lifestyle and eating habits
Sharon said she was doing this first for
herself secondly she said she wants to
live a long healthy life for and with
her children and future grandchildren
and lastly she is also doing it for her
fans because they deserve the best
version of their idol do you think
Sharon's ten step guide will work for
you are they too hard or are they do
above write your comments below if you
have a weight loss story to share then
go ahead and write that as well don't
forget to give this video a thumbs up
and if you haven't subscribed yet click
the subscribe button and we'd love to
keep you updated with our new videos so
I'll see you on the next one god bless